<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Trails in the sky: the story’s guide</string>
    <string name="Bracer_mss_1">Bracer_message_1</string>
    <string name="Bracer_mss_2">Bracer_message_2</string>
    <string name="main_title_btn">Titles</string>
    <string name="main_chars_btn">Characters</string>
    <string name="main_countries_btn">Countries</string>
    <string name="main_timeline_btn">Timeline</string>
    <string name="main_org_btn">Organizations</string>
    <string name="main_vid_btn">Videos</string>

    <string name="Bracer_statement_1">This app is sponsored by
        crown princess Kloe von Auslese of Liberl and created by ZCF.</string>
    <string name="Bracer_statement_2">In recent years, Zemuria has gone through many major incidents.
    This app is created in order to help Bracers, especially new Bracers,
        to be informed with necessary information.\' notes and guides.</string>

    <string name="title_sc_Summary">The Legend of Heroes: Trails in the Sky is first of Trails franchise.\n
        The Japanese name of the game is Eiyuu Densetsu Shikusu: Sora no Kiseki FC for pc.\n
        Let\'s explore what happens to Liberl of Zemuria continent in recent years.\n\n\n
        Summary:\n\n
        The story follows Estelle Bright and Joshua Bright, who just become junior Bracers from Liberl,
        are on their quest to become senior Bracers. The condition is to go to each major region in Liberl
        to earn recommendation letters from each Bracer Guild branch. In order to receive the letters, they must
        fulfill citizens\' requests to show their capabilities.\n\n
        However, their journeys are unlike any normal junior Bracers. The time they start their journeys was also
        when the coup planned by ex-Colonel Alan Richard was set in motion and close to final step.\n\n
        The Brights faced with many incidents that were rooted from the coup\'s plan in each region of Liberl,
        but they were unable to notice the plan as it was carefully hidden in multiple layers.\n\n
        During the kidnap incident of Prof. Albert Russell in Zeiss, together with C-rank bracer Agate Crosner,
        they were able to identify Colonel Richard was the source of all incidents the Brights dealt with.
        They also learnt the upcoming coup d\'teat would happen on the 60th Birthday Celebration of
        Queen Alicia von Auslese in Grancel.\n\n
        The Brights secretly informed the Guild to let every Bracer aware of the situation. However, under the
        law of Bracer Guild, we were unable to officially counter the coup from happening.\n\n
        The Liberl Intelligence Division was able to kidnap princess Klaudia von Aulese as she was returning to
        Grancel to attend her grandmother\'s birthday, and the Royal Guard was accused of planning the coup
        during this time. The Guild was able to obtain such information and quickly made an emergency
        rescue mission at Erbe Royal Villa, where the princess was held in custody.\n
        Due to the law of Bracer Guild, again, we were unable to act at first. But the Brights were able to
        contact Capt. Schwarz of the Royal Guard to request a secret joint rescue mission between the Bracer Guild
        and the Royal Guard. Thanks to the Royal Guard acted as the bait to lure most of Intelligence Division force
        to the front of Erbe Royal Villa, the Bracers were able to infiltrate the villa without being noticed.\n
        The mission was a success. We were able to locate the princess and took her under protection. After that,
        the Royal Guard gained a foothold at Erbe Royal Villa to prepare for the coup. Princess Klaudia also requested
        the Bracer Guild, as a citizen of Liberl, to stop the coup. Her action allowed us to legally counter
        the Intelligence Division when the coup happened.\n\n
        During the coup, the Royal Guards attacked the Intelligence Division directly while our bracers, Estelle Brights
        and Schera Harvey, and princess Klaudia infiltrated the Grancel castle by an airship.
        During this time, Queen Alicia was held under custody by 2nd Lt. Lorence of the Intelligence Division
        while Colonel Richard and his men were at the bottom of the castle to prepare for their final objective.\n
        The bracers and princess Klaudia were able to rescue Queen Alicia from 2nd Lt. Lorence.
        However, the reason was he gave up his mission due to his true identity and objective were different
        (More information in Trails in the Sky: SC).\n
        The Brights and several Bracers fought against Colonel Richard at the underground of Grancel castle. They were
        able to win against the Colonel, however, his plan was successful, which leaded to the attack from the Society
        one month later. The purpose of the coup will be explained in SC.\n\n
        S-rank bracer Cassius Bright returned to be Brigadier General of Liberl as he was during The Hundred Days War,
        which left S-rank bracer position empty for a long time. Liberl\'s peace returned for a very short period of time
        before the Society, Ouroboros, began their next step of Gospel Project.\n\n\n
        Note:\n
        Bracers who were involved in Liberl\'s coup incident: Estelle Bright, Joshua Bright, Schera Harvey, Agate Crosner,
        Zin Vathek, Kurt Nardin, Carna, Grant, Anelace Elfead, Elnan, Cassius Bright.\n
        Others who involved in Liberl\'s coup incident: Olivier Leinheim (Prince Olivert Reise Arnor of Erebonia).\n
        Kloe Rinz (Princess Klaudia von Auslese of Liberl).
        Nial Burns and Dorothy Hyayyt from Liberl News\n\n
        Personal information that are revealed with consents from related parties:\n
        Joshua Bright, adopted son of Cassius Bright, was Enforcer XII from the Society. He was manipulated by
        Weissmann (Third Anguis of the Society) without knowing it. Joshua was Weissmann spy to observe Cassius Bright\'s
        and the Guild. He revealed the truth to Joshua during Queen Alicia\'s Birthday Celebration, which caused
        Joshua to left the Guild informally.
    </string>
    <string name="title_fc_Summary">STORY ID 11</string>
    <string name="title_3rd_Summary">STORY ID 12</string>

    <string name="country_liberl_summary">The Liberl Kingdom is located in southwestern Zemuria. Its mainland is
        bordered to the south by the Thetis Sea and to the west by an unnamed ocean; to the north by Erebonia;
        and to the east by Calvard. Its crest is a white falcon.\n
        The name Liberl comes from the Liber Ark, the floating city governed by Sept-terion Aureole during
        the ancient time of Zemuria.\n\n
        The collapse of Liber Ark:\n
        -   The Liber Ark is a floating island city that brings prosperity to its citizens.\n
        -   However, over time, the reliance on the Aureole led to a decline in morals and ethics.\n
        -   As the result, madness and despair were spread all over the population.\n
        -   Celeste D von Auslese decided to end their reliance on the Aureole.\n
        -   However, Aureole resisted and treated them as enemies to prevent Liber Ark\'s destruction.\n
        -   Celeste D von Auslese succeeded in sealing both Aureole and Liber Ark in a different dimension.\n
        -   Celeste established the Liberl Kingdom in approzimately S.1\n\n
        The modern era:\n
        -   The clash between aristocrats and commoners reached climax after 100 years since the founded day.\n
        -   Princess Cecilia was responsible for abolishing the difference in classes in Liberl.\n
        -   Aristocracy still exists in a very small portion and uncommon in Liberl nowadays.\n\n
        Hundred Days War:\n
        -   In spring S.1192, Imperial Army of Erebonia started invading Liberl.\n
        -   Liberl was losing fast due to Imperial Army\'s blitz strategy.\n
        -   Liberl turned the table with the large scale counter-attack by using newly-developed patrol ships.\n
        -   In S.1193, a peace treaty was signed by Liberl and Erebonia, which marks the end of the Hundred Days War.\n
        (Warning: the followings are top secret international information that must not be revealed to the public)\n
        -   The cause of war: a massacre at night of Hamel village of Erebonia, which was located near
            the border between two countries.\n
        -   There was sight of perpetrators wearing Liberl Army uniform and using Liber\'s weapons.\n
        -   The Hamel incident is buried to the darkness because there was no survivor and there\'s possibly
            a third party that caused the massacre.\n
        -   It was revealed by Anguis III of Ouroboros, Georg Weissmann that he was the one suggested
            to an unknown party to cause the Hamel incident.\n\n
        Coup d\'etat:\n
        -   In S.1202, Colonel Alan Richard of the Royal Army\'s Intelligence Division attempted a coup.\n
        -   He was stopped by a joint force between the Royal Guardsmen, the Bracer Guild, ZCF, and princess Claudia.\n
        -   The true perpetrator was Georg Weissmann of the Society.\n
        -   The coup was prevented, however, the Gospel Plan of the Society was a success, which later led to the
            Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon.\n\n
        Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon:\n
        -   In S.1203, a country-wide Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon occurred, which disabled all orbal devices and caused
            a mass panic.\n
        -   The phenomenon also affected south of Erebonia, which caused the Imperial Army almost breached the
            Hanken Gate again.\n
        -   Thanks to Princess Klaudia of Liberl, the bracers and Prince Olivier of Erebonia,
            the Imperial Army halted their
            advancement temporarily and allowed Liberl Army and Bracers some time to stop the phenomenon.\n
        -   Liber Ark collapsed and the phenomenon was prevented.\n
        -   S-rank bracer Cassius Bright retired and returned to his previous position as commander of Royal Army
            of Liberl.\n
        Interntional event:\n
        -   Before the Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon, Queen Alicia managed to host a Non-Aggression Pact between Liberl,
            Erebonia, and Calvard.\n
    </string>
    <string name="country_calvard_summary">The Republic of Calvard is located in the western Zemuria. It is \n
        bordered to the southwest by Liberl, to the west by Erebonia and Crossbell; to the northwest by \n
        Remiferia; and to the east by Ored.\n\n
        It was founded in S.1090 and is famous for its immigration policy that allows people from the East to live
        in Calvard.\n\n
        Republican revolution:\n
        -   Around S.1100, the country was struck with a financial disaster.\n
        -   Merchants from East Zemuria financially supported the revolution to overthrow the ruling monarchy.\n
        -   In S.1187, the passenger ship Eterna sank in Calvardian waters, resulted the dead of Crown Prince
            Judis von Auslese and his wife.\n\n
        Hundred Days War:\n
        -   During the war, Calvard was unable to quickly support its neighbor country, Liberl, against Erebonia\'s
            blitz strategy.\n
        Relationship with Erebonia:\n
        -   Their relationship gets worse after the completion of the orbal railgun cannons at Garrelia Fortress, located
            at easternmost border of Erebonia.\n
        -   Even after the successful Non-Aggression Pact hosted in Liberl, their relationship is still far from good.\n\n
        </string>
    <string name="country_erebonia_summary">The Erebonia Empire is located in western Zemuria. It is bordered to
        the east by Calvard and to the south by Liberl.\n\n
        War of the Lions:\n
        -   The death of emperor Valius V in S.947 and the assassination of his son, the fourth prince Orthos
            seizes power in a military coupe of Heimdallr and declares himself the new emeperor.\n
        -   Orthos declares to purge anyone who dares to oppose him which accelerate the civil war.\n
        -   Prince Dreichels started raising an army and departs from Nord Highlands, hoping to end the war and to
            bring back the peace of Erebonians.\n
        -   Dreichels brought the end to Orthos\' tyranny and became the new emperor of Erebonia.\n\n
        Border disputes:\n
        -   Both Erebonia and Calvard grew rapidly and became two most powerful nations in Zemuria.\n
        -   Their growths also means the expansion of territories.\n
        -   The territory that both sides try to get is later established as Crossbell State.\n\n
        Hundred Days War:\n
        -   The lost of Hamel led Erebonia to declare war on Liberl Kingdom.\n
        -   Thanks to the manpower and blitz strategy, they advanced extremely fast and Liberl was likely to lose at any time.\n
        -   Liberl counter attacked with patrol ships and pushed Imperial Army out of the country.\n
        -   Erebonia signed the peace treaty and apologized to Liberl.\n
        -   Gilliath Osborne was promoted to chancellor of blood and iron.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="country_crossbell_summary">Crossbell State, formerly known as Corssbell Province, is a lanlocked,
        self-governing demilitarised buffer state located in wester Zemuria. It is bordered by Erebonia to the west and
        by Calvard to the east.\n\n
        There are a lot of mysteries surrounding Crossbell dated back to the Dark Ages. Specifically the ancient bells
        that are located in several location in Crossbell States.\n
        The state has a very complex situation. Erebonia and Calvard have been hostile to each other for the ownership of
        Crossbell province. Crossbell State was established in S.1137I to prevent the bloodshed between them. In a sense,
        some can say it is a share property of both Erebonia and Calvard.\n
        In the present, Crossbell State is growing extremely fast due to its location allows trades between two super nations
        Erebonia and Calvard</string>

    <string name="TL_txtviewIntro">The Zemuria continent follows the Septian Calendar
        to the present day.\n
        Note that the timeline in this guide is incomplete. It only shows the major events that are
        considered necessary and related for Liberl\'s bracers.\n
        The history is divided into 3 eras:\n
        1. After the Septian Calendar (1~500AS).\n
        2. After the Dark Ages (500~1100AD).\n
        3. After the Orbal Revolution (1150AR~).\n
    </string>
    <string name="TL_txtview2">Before the Septian Calendar is the era which is told that Gods fought and
        mutually killed each other after a 100 days struggle.\n
        The Sky Goddess, Aidios, gave humanity the Sept-Terrion, seven sacred treasures which
        granted dominion over the land, skies, and seas. They were eventually separated dividing humanity
        to pursue the respective ideals. </string>
    <string name="TL_year1">The Great Collapese brought the end of the ancient Zemurian civilization.\n
        Celeste D. Auslese sealed the Aureole in another dimension with the floating city, Liber Ark.
        Liberl Kingdom was founded below after.\n
        Around 1 - 500AS, Erebonia Empire was founded.
    </string>
    <string name="TL_year82">The Grancel Cathedral was built in the kingdom\'s capital.</string>
    <string name="TL_year200">The Order of the Gralsritter was founded.</string>
    <string name="TL_year_B500">The Dark Ages began.</string>
    <string name="TL_year_A500">The Septian Church appeared as Aidios religion, ending the Dark Ages.</string>
    <string name="TL_year1100">Liberl\'s decree of nobility has been abolished.\n
        The Calvard Republic was born.</string>
    <string name="TL_year1150">The Orbal Revolution started after Professor C.Epstein invented
        the first orbment.\n Bracer Guild was founded.</string>
    <string name="TL_year1162">Princess Alicia II inherited the throne at the age of 20 after
        king Edgar III\'s death.</string>
    <string name="TL_year1192w">WARNING: Any information about Hamel Village is international top secret.
        Bracers must not reveal this information to any unrelated party to prevent the continuation of
        the Hundred Days War.\n
    </string>
    <string name="TL_year1192">Tragedy occurred at Hamel Village, which was near the border between
        Erebonia Empire and Liberl Kingdom. The Hundred Days War started during spring after.\n
        The Imperial Army of Erebonia declared war and immediately attacked Liberl.\n
        2 months later, Albert Russell developed military patrolships. This allowed Liberl to
        counter attacked the Imperial Army.\n
        The ceasefire was agreed between Liberl and Erebonia. The Hamel incident was buried in the darkness.\n
        The Hamel incident led Leonhardt and Joshua to join the Ouroboros.
    </string>
    <string name="TL_year1196">Renne Haywworth was abducted in Calvard Republic.
        Later rescued by Ouroboros. Renne joined Ouroboros.</string>
    <string name="TL_year1201">The Liberl Intelligence Division was established.</string>
    <string name="TL_year1202">Erebonian Bracer Guilds were attacked.\n
        Cassius Bright was requested to solve the incident.\n
        Liberlian airship, Linde, was attacked by Sky Bandit and gone missing.\n
        Junior bracers Estelle and Joshua Bright began their adventure in Liberl.\n
        The 60th annual Queen\'s Birthday.\n
        A non-aggression pact was signed in Liberl, between Liberl, Calvard, and Erebonia.</string>
    <string name="TL_year1203">The Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon caused nationwide panic in Liberl.\n
        Erebonia Empire army was in the verge of invading Liberl again because
        the phenomenon affected south Erebonia.\n
        Kevin Graham and Ries Argent recovered an ancient artifact from the collapsed Liber Ark.</string>

    <string name="bracer_guild_description">Bracer Guild is an international non-governmental organisation
        acting to keep the peace and protect civilians. Its members are called bracers.\n
        Due to its international and neutral nature, it often mediates between disputing powers from small to
        large scale. Such as the Hundred Days War, the coup in Liberl, and the Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon.
        However, at the same time, Bracer Guild\'s activities can be severely limited for its Guild Code.\n\n
        Guild Code contains laws that bracer guild and all bracers must follow. Simply put, bracers are not allowed
        to involve and interfere in any nation\'s dispute when no harm is likely to happen to civilians.\n
        However, the loophole in the Guild Code can be used to allow Bracers to act immediately. During the coup, a
        citizen\'s request can allow Bracer Guild to act immediately to protect citizens from harm.</string>
    <string name="gralsritter_description">The Gralsritter is an order within the Septian Church, responsible
        for the investigation and retrieval of ancient Zemurian artifacts.\n\n
        There are 6 principles Gralsritter must follow:\n
        -   Offer your soul to Goddess and your body to Her church.\n
        -   Protect the Sacraments.\n
        -   Swear loyalty to the Holy Father.\n
        -   Carry out your duties with dignity.\n
        -   Protect the peace and order of the three worlds.\n
        -   Heretics must be eliminated.\n\n
        Knight is a promoted class among the Gralsritter of the Septian Church. They are also tasked to
        support the Dominion they have been assigned to.\n\n
        Squire is a base class among the Gralsritter of the Septian Church.</string>
    <string name="dominion_description">Dominion has 12 special knights among the Gralsritter and acts as
        the organization leaders. The Dominion have been active for about a thousand years. A manifestation
        of a Stigma is required in order to be promoted to the rank of Dominion.\n</string>
    <string name="epstein_foundation_description">Epstein Foundation is dedicated to spread orbal technologies
        across Zemuria. It was found by the disciples of C.Epstein (father of orbal technology) after his death.\n
        The Epstein Foundation researches and manufactures orbments, specialising in information processing and
        communication.</string>
    <string name="zcf_description">Zeiss Central Factory (ZCF) is an orbment research facility located in Liberl.\n
        Initially, Albert Russell (a disciple of C.Epstein) formed a partnership with Zeiss Clockmaker\'s Union.\n
        Together, they establish the Zeiss Engineering Factory in S.1157 and created orbment outside of
        Epstein Foundation.\n
        In S.1160, King Edgar III of Liberl visited the factory and decided to donate a large amount of
        money to further its research. Thanks to King Edgar III, orbments began to spread like wildfire
        across the kingdom, bringing prosperity to the people of Liberl.\n
        In S.1173, Zeiss Engineering Factory is renamed to Zeiss Central Factory.\n
        In S.1182, Albert Russell resigned from his position as Factory Chief.\n
        In S.1190, ZCF publicly announced the Orbal Network, a joint venture between ZCF and the
        Epstein Foundation.</string>
    <string name="ouroboros_description">Ouroboros, also known as the Society, is a mysterious organization
        that operates from the shadows in Zemuria.\n
        With its access to powerful, talented agents, and the latest technological advances that surpass any
        cutting edge technologies in Zemuria, it is involved in many major incidents that occur in Zemuria.\n
        It is unknown when Ouroboros was founded. The earliest record date back to S.1192, prior the Hundred
        Days War, but it is generally assumed that the Society has existed far longer than that.\n\n
        Gospel Plan:\n
        -   Their first publicly involvement is the coup led by Alan Richard in Liberl. The coup was a part of the
        Gospel Plan, that later caused the Liber Arc from the Dark Ages to reappeared in Liberl which caused
        Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon.\n
        -   The main objective of the Gospel Plan was to obtain Aureole, the Sept-Terrion
        of Space that controls the Liber Arc.\n
        -   The plan was guided by the third Anguis of the Society, Georg Weissmann.\n
        -   Georg Weissmann revealed that he was the mastermind that indirectly caused the Hundred Days War.\n\n
        In Trails in the Sky: The 3rd, it was revealed in the last secret door that Gospel Plan was just the first
        phase of Orpheus Final Plan, the main plan of the Society. After the Liber Arc incident, the Society is
        ready for the second phase, the Phantasmal Blaze Plan.\n\n
        Hierarchy:\n
        -   Grandmaster\n
        -   Anguis I, Campanella\n
        -   Anguis II - VII\n
        -   Enforcers\n
        -   Jaegers (mainly Red Constellation)

    </string>


</resources>
