<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="char_estelle">
        Estelle Bright is a bracer of Liberl. She is the main protagonist of Trails in the Sky FC and SC.\n
        She is Cassius Bright\'s daughter. She was Joshua Bright\'s sister but later turns into lover. Her homeland is Rolent in Liberl\n
        She started as a cheerful and optimistic tomboyish girl. She was not very smart, reckless, naive, and generally
            ignorant to the ways of the world. She is one of the kindest person in the series.\n\n
        During the Hundred Days War, she lost her mother, Lena, because of the collapse or Rolent Clock Tower
            that crushed her body. Estelle showed signs of being uncomfortable when she is near the rebuilted Clock Tower and
            when she hears someone talks about the war.\n\n
        In FC, her reckless and naive nature were her fatal flaw. So Joshua Bright had difficult time to slowly teach her the way
            she should act in some situations.\n
        She was worried about her father, Cassius Bright, after his disappearance.\n
        While she was working with Joshua to become senior bracer, she grew up mentally and gained many friends and allies.\n
        At the end of FC, she acknowledged that she loved Joshua. She was kissed by Joshua at night on the day of Queen Alicia
            birthday, but she was fainted later because Joshua drugged her a sleeping pill so that he could leave her.\n\n
        In SC, at the beginning, she was mentally ill and exhausted because she was trying to deny that Joshua left and abandoned her.
            She met a wander priest called Kevin Graham while on she was on her way back home because she was tricking herself to
            think Joshua just went home before her. Thanks to Father Kevin, Estelle managed to face the reality. With the helpf
            of her father and mentor, Scherazard, Estelle decided to train herself at Le Locle to improve herself.\n
        She made friend with Anelace during the training. After the training, she and other bracers were investigating on the Society.\n
        She had a strange affection for Renne despite she was a member of the Society. She tried to bring Renne out of the Society but failed
            due to her naive nature of not knowing the dark side of the society and human nature. However, she acknowledged her
            weakness and did not give up on Renne. Estelle managed to shake Renne\'s mind greatly at Liber Ark but Renne
            still refused her.\n
        In the 3rd, Estelle had become more mature but her optimistic and naive nature were still remained when she were with her friend. \n
            At the end, she said she was going to Crossbell, Renne\'s hometown and also where Renne was currently at. At this point,
            Estelle had managed to soften Renne\'s cold heart and selfishness and spoke her desire of wanting Renne to become her family.
  </string>

    <string name="char_gilbert">
        Gilbert Stein was mayor Dalmore\'s assitant during FC.\n
        Some time after he and Dalmore were arrested, he escaped and joined the Society.\n
        Gilbert is more of a comedy relief character in the series.\n
        For unknown reasons, he is Campanella\'s toy.\n
        In the 3rd final chapter, he is actually useful by attracting dragons\' attention away from Arseille so
            Estelle team can reach the Lord of Phantasma\'s palace safely.
    </string>

    <string name="char_giliath">
        Giliath Osborne, known as the Blood and Iron Chancellor of Erebonia.\n
        His motto is "Our nation\'s peace must be built on a foundation of blood and iron."\n
        He is known as a dangerous man and a monster to Olivier.\n
        In the 3rd, it shows that Olivier wants to overthrow Giliath due to his extreme nature of doing things. However, Giliath
            is popular among the Erebonia citizens, so any bad attempts will make citizens turn against Olivier.
    </string>

    <string name="char_grant">
        Grant is a senior bracer of Liberl.\n
        Estelle first meets him during the Grancel tournament.\n
        He has been a good bracer and ally of the people.
    </string>

    <string name="char_gustav">
        Gustav is the maintenance chief at ZCF.\n
        During the kidnap of professor Albert, chief Murdoch informed him the situation and helped Estelle\'s team to
            infiltrate Leiston Fortress.
    </string>

    <string name="char_hilda">
        Hilda is the Head Maid at Grancel Castle who serves Queen Alicia directly.\n
        In FC, in order to meet Queen Alicia, Estelle and Joshua have to met Hilda to let her know the upcoming coup.
            Thanks to her arrangement, Estelle and Joshua disguise themselves as new maids who are handpicked by Hilda
            herself to serve Queen Alicia.
    </string>

    <string name="char_jean">
        Jean is a Bracer Guild receptionist at Ruan.
    </string>

    <string name="char_josette">
        Josette Capua is a member of the Capua family.\n
        She was originally an Erebonian noble until they lost all of their fortune (except Bobcat) to a corrupt deal.\n\n
        In FC, she was the first enemy who tried to steal a precious gift of Mayor Klaus which was intentionally the gift
            for Queen Alicia in her Anniversary. She disguised herself as an honest student who loved to learn about the town.
            Her plan was busted but she managed to escape thanks to her older brother (Kyle) and his smokescreen.\n
        She and the entire Capua family were arrested and imprisoned by Colonel Richard until SC.\n\n
        In SC, she and the Capua family were rescued by Joshua, and they also stole back Bobcat. In exchange, the family had
            to help Joshua land on the Glorious. During the time Joshua worked with them, Josette fell in love with him. She
            was mad when Joshua always tried to distance himself from everyone else. But in the end, Don suggested to go extra miles
            to help Joshua even though their deal was completed. Thanks to that, the family saved Joshua and Estelle when they were
            gunning down by the Society soldiers.\n
        During the Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon, the Bobcat crashed on the Liber Ark. The whole family except Josette managed to escape
            the Society soldiers. Estelle team later found her and help her save the family.\n
        While she knows Joshua loves Estelle, she always hints that she is always be there for Joshua in romantic relationship.\n\n
        In the 3rd, she was sealed inside the stone and located in Bobcat inside the Phantasma. At this time, the family was forgiven
            and rewarded by Queen Alicia. The Capua bandit turned to legit business, sky delivery. In this game, we also learn
            a few more things about Josette, that she is a kind person, good at cooking and taking care of others.
    </string>

    <string name="char_joshua">
        Joshua Bright, formerly known as Joshua Astray, is the secondary protagonist of Trails in the Sky FC and SC.\n
        He was resident of Hamel village until the Tragedy of Hamel Village broke out. Only Joshua and Loewe survived the
            massacre. However, the tragedy killed every Hamel residents and his sister, Karen, broke Joshua\'s heart.\n
        In order to save him, Loewe and Joshua joined the Society. Joshua was fixed by Georg Weissmann but unknowingly became
            his puppet.\n
        Joshua and Loewe climbed to become Enforcer No. XII and Enforcer No.II of the Society.\n
        During one of their mission, they destroyed a brothel callde Paradise, rescued Renne Hayworth, and recruited her into the
            organizaiton as an enforcer.\n\n
        In S.1197, Joshua was ordered by Weissmann to assassinate Cassius Bright. He failed the task but was adopted as Cassius\'
            son. He was extremely unfriendly and prepared to get rid of by the Society after his failure but there was no one came
            after him. Thanks to Estelle, he slowly opened himself up and became a decent person.\n\n
        In FC, Joshua and Estelle became junior bracers and started their adventure to become senior bracer while searching for
            their father. Joshua was calm and intelligent, however, there were times that he acted very cold-blooded.\n
        During the Queen Alicia anniversary, professor Alba revealed himself as Georg Weissmann and revealed to Joshua that he
            was a spy for him since Joshua lived in Cassius\' house. Georg offered him a chance to return to the society but he refused.\n
        Joshua was shaken from what he learnt, he decided to leave everyone behind, especially Estelle, for their safety. On the night
            of the anniversay, when Estelle confessed her feeling to Joshua, he kissed her with a sleeping drug and brought her back
            to her room then left her to get his revenge on Georg.\n\n
        In SC, Joshua freed the Capua bandits and stole back their Bobcat in exchange for a ticket to infiltrate the Glorious of the Society,
            where Georg was currently at.\n
        During his time with the Capua bandit, Josette Capua fell in love with him but he always distanced himself away from
            everyone. Even so, after the deal was completed. The Capua family decided to go extra miles to help Joshua. They saved
            Joshua and Estelle when they were gunning down by a gun ship.\n
        Thanks to Estelle, Joshua finally accepted to come back with her. He was slapped by his father for making everyone
            worry about him. But his father later hugged him and was glad that he had returned safely.\n
        Queen Alicia apologized to Joshua for silencing the dead of every Hamel resident and not bringing justice for them.
            Joshua forgave her and said Queen Alicia only did what was right to protect her country.\n
        Joshua had several private talks with Father Kevin after that. It was revealed that he asked Kevin to free him from
            Georg\'s brainwash technique. Thanks to Kevin, Joshua managed to betray Georg when he ordered Joshua to kill Estelle.\n
        Joshua had a one-on-one battle against Loewe at Liber Ark. He managed to disarm  Loewe and convince Loewe to stop being an enforcer.
            Joshua was extremely happy when Loewe said he might follow his original dream, being a bracer.
            Sadly, Loewe was struck by Georg for 2 times which killed Loewe in the end. Loewe\'s dead made Joshua mentally collapsed again
            but Estelle reminded him Loewe\'s last words to motivate his will to live again. Joshua could not take Loewe\'s body
            with him while escaping the collapsing Liber Ark, so he took Loewe\'s sword with him.\n
        At the end of SC, Joshua placed his sword next to Karen\'s grave and decided to leave Liberl to go to
            many places, to help people and work to help people as his redemption. Estelle followed him as they were trying to
            find Renne.
    </string>

    <string name="char_julia">
        Julia Schwarz is the First Lieutenant of the Royal Army of Liberl. She is promoted to the rank of Captain.\n
        She is a talented swordwoman who was trained by Cassius Bright when he was an instructor. She was a friend and rival
            of Kanone Amalthea back in the Royal Academy days.\n
        She is a loyal servant and friend of Princess Klaudia. Her bird pet Sieg is a friend and a long distance communication bird
            between her and Klaudia.\n\n
        In FC, she received the message from Klaudia about the evil scheme of Mayor Dalmore. Thanks to that, she captured Dalmore
            by Arseille at the sea.\n
        Before the coup, Julia and the Royal Army fought against the Intelligence Division and tried to protect Klaudia but failed.
            After the clash, only her and few members escaped unnoticed. She sought help from Estelle and Joshua. Thanks to their
            cooperation, Bracer Guild also lent a hand to help them free the Erbe Royal Villa and save Klaudia.\n
        During the coup, she led the Royal Army to gather attention while bracers sneaked into Grancel to save the Queen and defeat
            colonel Richard.\n\n
        In SC, she was associated with Kevin Graham due to the mystery of Grancel\'s underground. She has a good relationship
            with Mueller Vander which makes Olivier teases them occasionally but only Mueller understood the circumstance and got mad
            at Olivier.\n\n
        In the 3rd, Julia was promoted to Captain but she didn\'t consider herself worthy enough for the title. Thanks to Mueller,
            she gave up on thinking too hard about it and motivated to work hard to serve Klaudia and the country like how she always be.
    </string>

    <string name="char_kanone">
        Kanone Amalthea is secretary at RA Research and the former Captain of the Intelligence Division of the Royal Army of Liberl.\n
        Kanone has a sadistic personality, strict, and sly.\n
        The only person she shows her greatest respect is Colonel Richard.\n
        In FC during the coup, she was defeated by Klaudia, Estelle, and Schera. But after the coup, she and several members escaped
            and planned to save Colonel Richard in the future.\n
        In SC, she kidnapped Duke Dunan and took him inside a tank to attack Grancel directly. Using the gospel to shutdown all
            orbal devices in Grancel except the tank made her almost invincible until Kevin used Dalmore\'s artifact to destroy
            the gospel.\n
        She and the rest of the division were captured in the end. She refused to cooperate with Julia about any information about
            the Society despite being toyed by them. Her stubbornness ended when Cassius let Richard meet her to let her understand
            that he no longer desires to walk on the path he used to walk anymore and is looking for his new path.\n
        During the attack of Society at Grancel, she led the Intelligence Division to fight against the Society army while Richard
            was at the Castle to aid Estelle\'s team against the Enforcers.\n\n
        In the 3rd, she retires and becomes the co-founder of RA Research with Richard.
    </string>

    <string name="char_karna">
        Karna ia a bracer of Ruan in Liberl.\n
        In FC, she was attacked by the Intelligence Division because of the 10 millions Mira her client was holding.\n
        Estelle team met her again during the Grancel tournament.\n
        She has been one of the bracers that supports Estelle team in the series.
    </string>

    <string name="char_kevin">
        Kevin Graham, was known as Heretic Hunter and later the Thousand-Hand Guardian, is a knight of the Gralsritter of
            the Septian Church and occupies the seat of Fifth Dominion.\n
        He first appears in SC as a wandering priest. He helped Estelle when she was on the brink of collapse due to Joshua left
            her. While working as a priest, he was investigating the Society and an ally to Estelle team.\n
        He was the one who executed Georg with an arrow made from the Salt Pale that turned over half of North Ambrian into salt.\n\n
        He is the main character of the 3rd. In this game, we learn that his father was a man who already had a family. His father
            provided support for him and his mother until one day he abandoned them, which caused his mother forced Kevin to commit
            double suicide with her. As a child, he was frightened, escaped, left his mother to kill herself, and had nowhere to go or return until he met Rufina
            Argent, a nun of the Church.\n
        Kevin worked hard to become Knight so he could protect what are important to him and made Rufina proud. However, jaegers attacked
            his orphanage. He swiftly defeated them except the last one taking Ries Argent as hostage. The last jaegar was panicked
            when he noticed Kevin so he grabbed the Magic Spear of Loa under the orphanage that turned him into a powerful monster. Kevin was not
            powerful enough to defeat the monster, but when the mosnter tried to hurt Ries. His stigma manifested and absorbed the power
            of the Demon Spear of Loa, and killed the monster. However, his power went berserk, and it took Rufina\'s life to return
            him to normal.\n
        The only way Kevin could think to redeem himself is to work himself to dead under the name of Heretic Hunter.\n
        The Phantasma abducted people who have relationship with him in order to fulfill his wish, that is to punish him.\n
        Thanks to Ries and his companions, he finally ended his nightmare by defeating the Lord of Phantasma, the ghost of Rufina.\n
    </string>

    <string name="char_kilika">
        Kilika Rouran, known as Crimson Swallow, is the aide of president Samuel Rocksmith and office manager of
            the Rocksmith Agency of Calvard. She worked as receptionist of Bracer Guild at Zeiss in Liberl.\n
        She is a beautiful woman who works extremely efficient.\n
        In SC, we learn that she is the daughter of Master Ryuga of the Taito School (master of Zin Vathek and Walter).\n
        She was Walter\'s lover when he was her father\'s student. After the dead of her father, their relationship ended.
            She decided to close the school and go travelling across the continent to find Walter in the hope of bringing him back.\n
        After SC, she was asked to return to Calvard and worked for Rocksmith. She was hesitated, but having a few talks with Zin made her
            make up her mind to accept the offer.
    </string>

    <string name="char_klaudia">
        Klaudia von Auselse, her other name is Kloe Rinz, is the granddaughter of Alicia von Auslese, and heir to the throne of Liberl Kingdom.\n
        Her parents died a year after her birth in S.1187 when the passenger ship Eterna sank off the coast of Calvard.\n
        During the Hundred Days War, Klaudia was separated from his escort and was taken in and raised by the matrons of
            Mercia Orphanage, Teresa and Joseph. When she returned to Ruan in S.1200 while studying at Jenis Royal Academy as Kloe Rinz,
            she learnt about Joseph\'s passing in an accident 4 years prior and decided to help Teresa to take care of the orphans.\n\n
        In FC, Estelle and Klaudia had a minor confront due to misunderstanding. Klaudia quickly became friend with Estelle and Joshua.\n
        She requested both of them to become actors for a play at her school festival. Her started falling in love with Joshua during
            the play. Her friendship with Estelle was strangely improved after she let Estelle know her true feeling.\n
        Klaudia was not happy when Teresa accepted mayor Morris money and a new orphanage after Mercia Orphanage was burned down by
            unknown party at that time. However, Klaudia understood that was necessary for Teresa and the orphans.\n
        Klaudia was extremely upset when she found out the Orphanage was burnt down by mayor Morris so that he can build a resort
            and sell it at high price for her uncle Dunan.\n
        While Morris was escaping the party, Klaudia already informed Julia via her falcon, Sieg, to capture him via Arseille.\n
        Klaudia hid her identity from Joshua and Estelle until they found her at Erbe Royal Villa.\n\n
        In SC, Klaudia was distraught about her being worthy to be the next heir. Duke Dunan criticized her made her aware of her
            weaknesses further. Bleublanc was excited to see the fall of Klaudia when they first meet.\n
        At the end of SC, Klaudia acknowledged her weaknesses and did not let it prevent her from improving herself to be the
            crown princess. Bleublanc confessed that he fell in love with her, not as a tragic princess but a strong and beautiful one.\n
        In the 3rd, she confessed her feeling to Joshua and was refused. However, she felt refresh and admitted her defeat.
    </string>

    <string name="char_klaus">
        Mayor Klaus is the mayor of the city of Rolent in Rolent region, Liberl.\n
        In FC, his house was attacked by the Capua bandits. No harm happened to him and anyone in the house but his
            gift for Queen Alicia was stolen. He asked Estelle and Joshua to help him retrieve it back.
    </string>

    <string name="char_kurt">
        Kurt Nardin, known as the Artful Tactician, is a bracer from Liberl.\n
        In FC, he was the one who sent the gospel to Cassius Bright but ended up in the hand of Estelle. He was attacked
            by the Intelligence Division for knowing the secret. He was alive because he was a bracer. Killing him may alert
            the entire Bracer Guild, and also Loewe tried to avoid needless bloodshed. As the result, he was brainwashed to
            erease his memory about the coup and anything related to them.\n
        In SC, he was the instructor who trained Estelle and Anelace at Le Locle training ground. He was promoted to A rank bracer.

    </string>

    <string name="char_kyle">
        Kyle Capua is a member of the Capua family.\n
        He was an Erebonian noble until the family lost everything but the Bobcat to a corrupt deal.\n
        In FC, he rescued Josette and other members when they were cornered by Estelle team. He and the family were
            arrested by Colonel Richard until SC.\n
        Since SC, Kyle and the family have been allies with Liberl and Estelle team.
    </string>

    <string name="char_lechter">
        Lechter Arundel is a commissioned major of the Intelligence Division of the Imperial Army of Erebonia. He is a member
            of the Ironbloods.\n
        He was a student and student president of Jenis Royal Academy in Liberl. He had a carefree nature that brought headaches
            to people around him. He was playing a fool most of the time, but his talent was what made him the student president.\n
        Kloe initially did not have a good impression of him. However, when Kloe had a quarrel with her roommate, Lecther gave her
            some advices to help her settle down the incident happily.\n
        It was said that he suddenly left the academy one day without anyone noticed.\n
        Klaudia met him again when he was with Giliath and learned the truth about him.
    </string>

    <string name="char_leonhardt">
        Leonhardt, his real name is Loewe. His fake name is Lorence Belgar. He is called Bladelord, Enforcer No. II of Ouroboros.\n
        He was a resident of Hamel Village until the tragedy happened. In order to save Joshua, he and Joshua joined the Society and climbed
            to the rank of Enforcer.\n
        In FC, he used Weissmann\'s manipulative power to hypnotize Kurt Nardin to interrogate him.\n
        In Ruan, he saved the Mercia orphans and Teresa from the burning orphanage. Agate had confronted him directly when
            he was chasing the members of Intelligence Division. Leonhardt noticed Agate weakness and pointed out his sword
            swinging aimlessly, which made Agate madder. According to the orphans, Leonhardt was at Jenis Academy festival but Joshua
            could not find him.\n
        During the coup, Queen Alicia realized Lorence was a survivor of Hamel from their conversation.\n\n
        In SC, Leonhardt mostly worked behind the scene until Ragnard was manipulated by Weissmann and was going to cause havoc to where ever
            it went. In order to minimize the damage, he was on its head trying to stop it breathing fire and cause damange in Bose. It is
            unknown how much damage he managed to reduce but no one lost their life. When Agate\'s hometown was burned again after
            the Hundred Days War, he was chasing after Leonhardt and fought him. Leonhardt found Agate pathetic and was going to kill him
            until Tita jumped out to stop him. After the dragon incident, Leonhardt visited Agate\'s village to pay his respect for
            those who lost their lives in the Hundred Days War. General Morgan, Agate, and Tita were there but no fight happened or anyone
            intended to fight because they do not want to disrespect the deads.\n
        At the end of SC, Joshua disarmed Leonhardt in a one-to-one fight. Leonhardt revealed his purpose of joining the Gospel plan
            was to test if humans were capable to improve themselves or kept being foolish, and to determine if Karin\'s dead
            was worth it. After the fight, he expressed his plan to retire from the Society and became bracer like how he used to wish for.
            He was struck by Weissmann and was unconscious. When Weissmann fused with Aureole and almost killed Estelle team, Leonhardt used
            his sword, Kernviter, which was bestowed to him by the Grandmaster to break through Weissmann\'s invincibility and caused damage
            to him. However, Leonhardt received a mortal damage which later killed him. Before he died, he asked Estelle to take care
            of Joshua.\n
        In the 3rd, he was the servant of Lord of Phantasma. Before his body disappeared, Joshua told him that he placed Kernviter
            next to Karin\'s grave and he had move on to live. Leonhardt was glad to hear that and died in peace.

    </string>

    <string name="char_lila">
    </string>

    <string name="char_luciola">
    </string>

    <string name="char_lugran">
    </string>

    <string name="char_maybelle">
    </string>

    <string name="char_morgan">
    </string>

    <string name="char_morris">
    </string>

    <string name="char_mueller">
    </string>

    <string name="char_murdoch">
    </string>

    <string name="char_olivier">
        Olivert Reise Arnor, also known in diguise as the bard Olivier Lenheim, is the oldest son of Emperor Eugent III and the prince of Erebonia.\n
        Despite not being the crown prince, he still works hard to improve his country. He became aware of the growing danger
            of Giliath Osborne and went to seek Caissus Bright\'s help to have an arranged marriage between himself and Princess
            Klaudia.\n\n
        In FC, he first appears as an idiot. Playing bard and singing songs to break any tensions. He followed Estelle party like
            it was a natural thing to do. He had been a major help for Estelle and her friends since the beginning of the series.
            Scherazard hit the mark when she was suspicious about Olivier being an Erebonian spy, but she did not know he was the prince.\n\n
        In SC, he learnt that Estelle returned after her training so he came to meet and joined her party again.\n
        He had a strange rivalry relationship with Enforcer No. X Bleublanc about their views of love.\n
        He left the party and came back to Erebonia before Erebonia army was breaching through Hanken Gate due to the Orbal Shutdown
            Phenomenon that affected south Erebonia. He met the party again as Olivert Reise Arnor and requested princess Klaudia to
            bring Erebonian army to Liberl soil to help Liberl solve the incident. Thanks to Princess Klaudia\'s negotiation and plots behind
            the scene with Cassius Bright, Olivert managed to halt the advancement for a limited period of time.\n
        He quickly joined the party again as Olivier with his bodyguard Mueller to help the party solve the incident.\n\n
        In the 3rd, Olivier showed discomfort about Giliath. He deemed Giliath was too dangerous due to his aggressive nature that could led
            Erebonia to the civil war with the Erebonian nobles.\n
        Before Olivier left the Phantasma, he asked Schera to consider his proposal which shocked Estelle.
</string>

    <string name="char_philip"></string>

    <string name="char_renne"></string>

    <string name="char_ries"></string>

    <string name="char_rufina"></string>

    <string name="char_scherazard">
        Scherazard Harvey, known as the Silver Streak, is a bracer of Liberl.\n
        In FC, she was a strict but kind to her students, Estelle and Joshua. She highly respected Cassius Bright whom saved
            her from her past crisis.\n
        Her alcohol tolerance is extremely high, which caused countless nightmare to Olivier and his gut.\n
        When she learnt about Joshua\'s past, she had a very complex emotion. Cassius asked her how she trully felt about the situation,
            the she replied that Cassius and Joshua were the "two most wrechedly miserable son of dogs" that she had ver known.\n
        In SC, it was revealed that Schera was a member of the Harvey circus. However, the circus master was preparing to sell the circus
            to a rich man so he could leave them with his debt on his shoulder. Luciola, whom Schera thought as an older sister, who was in love
            with Mr. Harvey, felt betrayed and pushed him off the cliff so that he could never leave her.\n
        Schera first met Luciola again during an mist incident at Rolent. After Luciola was defeated at Liber Ark, she told
            Schera everything and jumped off the Liber Ark. Schera attempted to save her by wrapping her whip on Luciola\'s arm,
            but Luciola cut the whip and fell down.\n\n
        In the 3rd, Luciola reappeared in Phatasma. Schera asked if that meant Luciola was still alive, Luciola of the Phantasma
            said she had no idea and left Schera to figure it out on her own.\n
        At the end of the 3rd, it seemed there was a romantic relationship between her and Olivier.
    </string>

    <string name="char_teresa"></string>

    <string name="char_tita">
        Tita Russell is the granddaughter of Albert Russell. She lives with him in Zeiss.\n
        She is a prodigy in orbal technology thanks to her family influence.\n
        In FC, her grandfather was kidnapped by the Intelligence Division. She went with Estelle and Joshua and tried to rescue
            him. But she accidentally agitated them and Agate had to jump out and receive a deadly poisonous bullet. She felt
            guilty about her mistake so she worked hard to take care of Agate and was called Mischa by Agate while he mistook
            Tita for his sister. Tita was curious about Mischa but Agate did not tell her about Mischa was dead.\n
        Tita slowly became fond of Agate and got used to his foul-mouth and rude attitude.\n\n
        In SC, she joined the party again when Estelle came to Zeiss. She became friend with Renne in Grancel for a short period of time.
            After knowing Renne was an Enforcer, she shared the same thought with Estelle: she wanted to help Renne and became her
            true friend.\n
        After the dragon burned down Agate village, he rushed to Loewe to settle his score. She jumped out to stop Loewe
            from killing Agate. When she finally learned about Mischa, she was sad when Agate kept
            insulting himself out of self-hatred. She was upset because Agate was insulting the Agate that she cared about. Thanks to her,
            Agate finally managed to forgive himself.\n
        In the 3rd, when Renne first appeared in Phantasma, she was agitated and almost had a fight with the rest. It was Tita
            came out to stop both sides.\n
        In a secret door, it showed that her mother, Erika Russell, did not like Agate due to his punk like appearance and attitude.\n
            Tita also faced the moral issue of being a scientist when she was trying to learn about Renne\'s Pater-Mater.
            In the end, her desire to help people made her aware of the dangerous of technologies but also their benefits
            for the people.
    </string>

    <string name="char_walter"></string>

    <string name="char_zin">
        Zin Vathek, known as the Immovable, is an A=rank bracer of Calvard. He is a fighter of Taito martial art.\n
        In FC, Estelle first met him as a solo fighter of the Grancel tournament. In order for her to meet Queen Alicia to
            inform her about the truth about the Intelligence Division, she asked him to become his teammate to win the
            tournament and meet the queen.\n
        Zin was a reliable ally and senior of the party.\n\n
        In SC, Estelle team and Zin learned that his senior, Walter, was Enforcer No. VIII of the Society.\n
        The party almost got killed when they first faced Walter, but Zin managed to come in time and save them.\n
        In the end, Zin defeated Walter in a one-on-one battle. It was revealed that Walter killed their master in a deadmatch
            but Zin told Walter that their master was diagnosed with a malignant tumour and his days were numbers.
    </string>

</resources>
