<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Trails in the sky: the story’s guide</string>
    <string name="Bracer_mss_1">Bracer_message_1</string>
    <string name="Bracer_mss_2">Bracer_message_2</string>
    <string name="main_title_btn">Titles</string>
    <string name="main_chars_btn">Characters</string>
    <string name="main_countries_btn">Countries</string>
    <string name="main_timeline_btn">Timeline</string>
    <string name="main_org_btn">Organizations</string>
    <string name="main_vid_btn">Videos</string>

    <string name="Bracer_statement_1">This app is sponsored by
        crown princess Kloe von Auslese of Liberl and created by ZCF.</string>
    <string name="Bracer_statement_2">In recent years, Zemuria has gone through many major incidents.
    This app is created in order to help Bracers, especially new Bracers,
        to be informed with necessary information.\' notes and guides.</string>

    <string name="title_fc_Summary">The Legend of Heroes: Trails in the Sky is first of Trails franchise.\n
        The Japanese name of the game is Eiyuu Densetsu Shikusu: Sora no Kiseki FC for pc.\n
        Let\'s explore what happens to Liberl of Zemuria continent in recent years.\n\n\n
        Summary:\n\n
        The story follows Estelle Bright and Joshua Bright, who just become junior Bracers from Liberl,
        are on their quest to become senior Bracers. The condition is to go to each major region in Liberl
        to earn recommendation letters from each Bracer Guild branch. In order to receive the letters, they must
        fulfill citizens\' requests to show their capabilities.\n\n
        However, their journeys are unlike any normal junior Bracers. The time they start their journeys was also
        when the coup planned by ex-Colonel Alan Richard was set in motion and close to final step.\n\n
        The Brights faced with many incidents that were rooted from the coup\'s plan in each region of Liberl,
        but they were unable to notice the plan as it was carefully hidden in multiple layers.\n\n
        During the kidnap incident of Prof. Albert Russell in Zeiss, together with C-rank bracer Agate Crosner,
        they were able to identify Colonel Richard was the source of all incidents the Brights dealt with.
        They also learnt the upcoming coup d\'teat would happen on the 60th Birthday Celebration of
        Queen Alicia von Auslese in Grancel.\n\n
        The Brights secretly informed the Guild to let every Bracer aware of the situation. However, under the
        law of Bracer Guild, we were unable to officially counter the coup from happening.\n\n
        The Liberl Intelligence Division was able to kidnap princess Klaudia von Aulese as she was returning to
        Grancel to attend her grandmother\'s birthday, and the Royal Guard was accused of planning the coup
        during this time. The Guild was able to obtain such information and quickly made an emergency
        rescue mission at Erbe Royal Villa, where the princess was held in custody.\n
        Due to the law of Bracer Guild, again, we were unable to act at first. But the Brights were able to
        contact Capt. Schwarz of the Royal Guard to request a secret joint rescue mission between the Bracer Guild
        and the Royal Guard. Thanks to the Royal Guard acted as the bait to lure most of Intelligence Division force
        to the front of Erbe Royal Villa, the Bracers were able to infiltrate the villa without being noticed.\n
        The mission was a success. We were able to locate the princess and took her under protection. After that,
        the Royal Guard gained a foothold at Erbe Royal Villa to prepare for the coup. Princess Klaudia also requested
        the Bracer Guild, as a citizen of Liberl, to stop the coup. Her action allowed us to legally counter
        the Intelligence Division when the coup happened.\n\n
        During the coup, the Royal Guards attacked the Intelligence Division directly while our bracers, Estelle Brights
        and Schera Harvey, and princess Klaudia infiltrated the Grancel castle by an airship.
        During this time, Queen Alicia was held under custody by 2nd Lt. Lorence of the Intelligence Division
        while Colonel Richard and his men were at the bottom of the castle to prepare for their final objective.\n
        The bracers and princess Klaudia were able to rescue Queen Alicia from 2nd Lt. Lorence.
        However, the reason was he gave up his mission due to his true identity and objective were different
        (More information in Trails in the Sky: SC).\n
        The Brights and several Bracers fought against Colonel Richard at the underground of Grancel castle. They were
        able to win against the Colonel, however, his plan was successful, which leaded to the attack from the Society
        one month later. The purpose of the coup will be explained in SC.\n\n
        S-rank bracer Cassius Bright returned to be Brigadier General of Liberl as he was during The Hundred Days War,
        which left S-rank bracer position empty for a long time. Liberl\'s peace returned for a very short period of time
        before the Society, Ouroboros, began their next step of Gospel Project.\n\n\n
        Note:\n
        Bracers who were involved in Liberl\'s coup incident: Estelle Bright, Joshua Bright, Schera Harvey, Agate Crosner,
        Zin Vathek, Kurt Nardin, Carna, Grant, Anelace Elfead, Elnan, Cassius Bright.\n
        Others who involved in Liberl\'s coup incident: Olivier Leinheim (Prince Olivert Reise Arnor of Erebonia).\n
        Kloe Rinz (Princess Klaudia von Auslese of Liberl).
        Nial Burns and Dorothy Hyayyt from Liberl News\n\n
        Personal information that are revealed with consents from related parties:\n
        Joshua Bright, adopted son of Cassius Bright, was Enforcer XII from the Society. He was manipulated by
        Weissmann (Third Anguis of the Society) without knowing it. Joshua was Weissmann spy to observe Cassius Bright\'s
        and the Guild. He revealed the truth to Joshua during Queen Alicia\'s Birthday Celebration, which caused
        Joshua to left the Guild informally.
    </string>
    <string name="title_sc_Summary">
        Trails in the Sky SC is the second installment in the Trails series and the second installment of the Liberl arc.\n\n
        After Joshua left Estelle at the end of FC, she was heart-broken and lied to herself that Joshua just went back
        home in Rolent. On her way back via airship, she met a strange travelling priest of Septian Church,\n
        called Kevin Graham, who doesn\'t act like one at all. It was thanks to Kevin that Estelle accepted the truth that
        Joshua left her and will never come home again. With the help of her father (Cassius Bright) and
        her mentor (Scherazard Harvey), Estelle moved Le Locle in Leman for a special training camp for bracers.\n
        At Le Locle, Estelle met Anelace Elfead again and trained together over two months.\n
        Meanwhile, Julia Schwarz escorts Kevin to the sealed facility under Grancel and shows him the remnants of the
        Reverie. He comments that he has seen something like this before in Calvard.\n
        After the training, Estelle and Anelace becomes friendly rival. They return to Grancel together. Enal requests
        them to investigate the Society by solving strange cases that are happening all over Liberl. Estelle can choose
        to tag with Schera or Agate to investigate in Ruan. (Let\'s assume Estelle tags with Schera).\n
        The society, Ouroboros, is preparing for the next phaase of Gospel Plan. It was revealed the a jaegar group,
        called Jester, which was trained under Loewe, was annihilated in Erebonia by Cassius Bright. But Jester had
        accomplished their mission, to get Cassius outside of Liberl during FC.\n
        Joshua secretly works with Capua family to help them steal back the Bob Cat, Capua\'s airship. While they
        are on their way to reach the Bob Cat, they visit the remain of Hamel.\n\n

        Chapter 1: Sneaking Shadows\n
        -   Estelle returns to Ruan.\n
        -   Estelle met several old friends: Kloe, Olivier.\n
        -   Kloe confesses that she\'s in love with Joshua. Estelle and Kloe remains friend even closer than before.\n
        -   As a team of four, they investigate the case of a mystery floating ghost, which has been reported by several
            residents in the whole region.\n
        -   During the investigation, they meet a happy family with their young daughter named Renne.\n
        -   The party meets Kevin who is teaching the orphans at Sunday School.\n
        -   The identity of the ghost was Enforcer X, the Phantom Thief, named Bleublanc.\n
        -   It was thanks to Dorothy with her camera to save the party from Bleublanc\'s shadow bind.\n
        -   The party manages to solve the ghost incident but Bleublanc left because he has accomplished his mission.\n
        -   At the end of chapter, it was revealed that father Kevin is also investigating the Ouroboros.\n\n
        Chapter 2: The Raging Land\n
        -   This chapter takes place in Zeiss.\n
        -   The mystery case is about the unnatural earthquakes.\n
        -   The team learns that there\'s a man wearing black clothes and sunglasses appears at locations where the
            earthquake happens.\n
        -   The party meets Tita Russell again. She joins the party. The party also meets Agate and Anelace for a short period of time.\n
        -   The party manages to locate the next possible location for earthquake, the cave near Elmo at the hot springs.\n
        -   This time, the party faces a new enemy of the Society, Enforcer VIII, The Direwolf, named Walter. He fought the
            entire party effortlessly. Fortunately, Zin Vathek arrives to save the day. It turns out that Walter studied under the
            same master a long time ago: Kilika\'s father.\n
        -   At the end of the chapter, Kanone is plotting to free Colonel Richard.\n\n
        Chapter 3: The Mad Tea Party\n
        -   The chapter takes place in Grancel.\n
        -   A major event is going to take place in Grancel, the discuss of a non-aggression pact and copies of Liberl\'s
            best airship, Arseille to both Erebonia and Calvard.\n
        -   This time, Kanone is preparing to attack Grancel and demands the release of Colonel Richard.\n
        -   The party meets Duke Dunan at Erbe Royal Villa. He is still bitter about what happened at the end of FC.\n
        -   The party meets Renne again and learns that her parents are nowhere to be found. It is also possible that Renne
            was abandoned. So the party keeps Renne with them until they can find her parents.\n
        -   Meanwhile, the party is helping the government to make sure the event goes smoothly.\n
        -   Anelace and Agate found a hideout of several runaway members of Intelligence Division and fought them.\n
        -   Enforcer 0, The Fool, Campanella shows his face to Agate and Anelace and burns ID\'s members to dead. However,
            all of the ID\'s members were not humans but robots. Agate and Anelace learn about a "Tea Party" which is going
            to happen soon.\n
        -   In a different place, the Capuas and Joshua destroys those robot soldiers and also learn about the Tea Party.\n
        -   Late afternoon of the second day, Renne told Estelle that a boy whom Renne describes just like Joshua, asked her
            to give Estelle a letter. The letter asks Estelle to meet Joshua at Gurune Gate.\n
        -   Estelle arrives to find Kevin, who also received a similar letter. It turns out to be a trap from the Society, they
            were attacked by a powerful robot from Society, Archaisms.\n
        -   Estelle and Kevin hurries back to the guild after they defeated the Archaisms. They find everyone in the Guild is
            drugged by a strong sleeping bills and there is no life threatening situation. But Renne is nowhere to be found.\n
        -   Agate comes not long after the incident and joins the party to save Duke Dunnan from Kanone
            by the request of his butler, Philip.\n
        -   Kanone and several ID\'s members piloting a tank equipped with a Gospel device that disable all orbment devices in
            Grancel. Kevin used the Artifact that Mayor Dalmore used to temporarily shutdown the Gospel. Julia joins the party
            to fight the tank.\n
        -   It turns out that Kanone was played by enforcer XV, the Angel of Slaughter, Renne. And the whole attempt to save Colonel
            Richard and the Gospel device activated in Grancel are her Tea Party. It was revealed that Renne\'s parents are faked,
            and she has a giant robot called Pater-Mater as her true parent. Renne says farewell and leaves without fighting.\n
        -   Kevin reveals that he is a squire in an order of the Church called the Gralsritter. He shares what he has been doing in
            Liberl in the name of Septian Church.\n
        -   While Kanone is being questioned, Casiuss Bright let Colonel Richard to meet her. Richard apologizes to Kanone,
            saying that his pride led to the ruin of so many people, hers included. He thanks her for doing everything for him
            but it is time for her to let it go. He has accepted full responsibility for everything and his fight is over.\n
        -   At an Ouroboros base, Renne seems to have good relationship with Loewe. She said the Tea Party was boring because she
            did not kill anyone. She wants Joshua to return to Ouroboros, and Weissmann says it is Estelle who is preventing
            Joshua to return.\n
        -   Before the party leaves to Ruan, Estelle receives a photo from Dorothy, showing Joshua was on the deck of the Bobcat while
            it was escaping from Liberl army.\n
        -   During the heist, it was revealed that Josette has a crush on Joshua, and Mueller (Olivier\' bodyguard) learns that
            Joshua is a Hamel\'s survivor.\n\n
        Chapter 4: The Mist Demon\'s Target\n
        -   The airship, which the party is onboard, is forced to land in Rolent due to unusual heavy fog.\n
        -   The fog is making residents worry more and more when there are several residents fall asleep and never wake up.\n
        -   The party also notices a strange bell ringing right before someone falls asleep.\n
        -   The culprit is enforcer VI, the Bewitching Bell, Luciola. Luciola was like a sister to Schera when Schera was in the
            circus called the Harvey Troupe. Schera\'s last name comes from the name Harvey from the troupe. It is unknown at
            this point why Luciola abandoned Schera and joined the Ouroboros, but Luciola provokes Schera to find the truth by
            chasing her.\n
        -   Before the party fights Luciola, they fell asleep by Luciola\'s power. When Estelle is sleeping, she dreams about
            her old time together with her mother who was still alive before the Hundred Days War. It was a happy dream but she
            later realizes that it was all the dream and she needs to move on and finds Joshua. Her mother says she\'s based on
            Estelle\'s real mother and everything happening right now is just a dream. Estelle\'s mother says she loves her and hopes
            Estelle to become strong and be happy.\n
        -   The incident is solved. The mist is gone, and the victims wake up from their dreams.\n\n
        Chapter 5: That Which One Must Protect\n
        -   The chapter takes place in Bose.\n
        -   Weissmann causes a dragon in the old legend of Liberl, Ragnard, to go crazy. It was thanks to Loewe who tries to stop his
            craziness. However, the damage is large.\n
        -   It was revealed that Agate used to have a younger sister named Mischa. Mischa died during Erebonia\'s attacks in
            the Hundred Days War. Her dead has been a trauma and a source of rage for Agate.\n
        -   Agate has a score to deal with Loewe so he is chasing after Loewe after the dragon wrecks havoc in Bose market.\n
        -   Loewe beats Agate while criticizing him for swinging his blade aimlessly. Tita manages to stop Loewe from killing Agate.\n
        -   General Morgan and his men come to capture Loewe and Ragnard but both of them fly away.\n
        -   Thanks to Tita taking care of Agate, he manages to overcome his pain, stop blaming himself for Mischa\'s dead,
        and lives.\n
        -   The party leaves Tita and Agate behind to board the Arseille to bring down Ragnard.\n
        -   The Ragnard is taken down and falls to the sea. However, the Gospel device on its head activated and causes it
            to go crazy and escape.\n
        -   In t second attempt to capture Ragnard, Agate\'s sword is equipped with a prototype unit of a device that can
        destroy Gospel device\'s function.\n
        -   The party destroys the Gospel device and frees Ragnard. Ragnard reveals that he is indeed the dragon in the legend.
            However, he cannot provide support to Liberl because of his promise with Aidios to simply watch over where Aureole sleeps
            and not to interfere in the lives of men. He also mentions that Cassius Bright was the last man he spoke with before
            taking his recent twenty year nap.\n
        -   Afterward, Agate and Tita stop by Ravennue to pay their respect to Mischa\'s grave and see general Morgan and
            even Loewe both have the same idea. General Morgain comes every year out of regret for the lives he was unable
            to save during the war. Loewe is there because both him and Agate lost their loved ones in the war. Loewe leaves
            peacefully, but he mentions the name Hamel which shocks Morgan.\n\n
        Chapter 6: The Whereabouts of Bonds\n
        -   Joshua uses the Bobcat to invade on an Ouroboros gunship to sneak into the Glorious. The contract between him and
            the Capuas is completed.\n
        -   While the party is taking a short break at Valleria Lake with Kevin, they found the injured Kurt on a boat. Kurt
            is awake and recovers his memory thanks to Kevin. He informs that he and several Bracers found a hideout of
            Ouroboros nearby. Only he managed to escape to report.\n
        -   The party sneaks into the Ouroboros hideout and rescue other Bracers, including Anelace. However, there is a trap
            on the top floor. Weissmann captured Estelle while the party was unconscious.\n
        -   Estelle found herself awake in the Glorious. Weissmann and Renne want her to join the Society, so Estelle can
            become stronger and be together with Joshua again.\n
        -   Estelle thinks deeply about it and decides to escape. Estelle is surrounded by jaegars in red but Joshua comes to
            rescue her. Loewe comes to stop them but Joshua declares that he has planted bombs all over the Glorious. So Loewe
            let them leave while trying to disable the bombs. They are stopped by Campanella at the hangar, however, he only
            wants to make their escape difficult because he is just an observer.\n\n
        Chapter 7: The Tetracyclic Towers\n
        -   Joshua and Estelle manages to escape the Glorious on an airship. However, they are being chased by gunships from
            the Glorious. But the Bobcat appears to make a surprise attack on the gunships and helps them escape.\n
        -   They manage to land down safely. Estelle is finally able to meet Joshua again brings him back home.\n
        -   Back to Grancel castle, Queen Alicia tells the tragic of Hamel and apologizes to Joshua. Joshua forgives her and
            he believes that is a sane decision a leader must make.\n
        -   Joshua has a secret talk with Kevin.\n
        -   The party learns that Duke Dunan is starting to develop into a responsible adult, helping Queen Alicia and
            Kloe. People start to respect him and change their opinion about him.\n
        -   Olivier leaves to return to the Empire.\n
        -   There are reports of a strange phenomenon happening at the four towers. The party is allowed to take the
            Arseille to investigate. At each tower, the inside turns into a very large dimension. On their way to the top,
            they find corrupted date from the Dark Ages. Each tower is responsible for each enforcer the party met during SC.\n
        -   After Walter is beaten, Kilika breaks up the solo fight between him and Zin. The party also learns that Walter and
            Kilika used to be lover, and Walter killed his former master (Kilika\'s father) in a duel.\n
        -   After Luciola is beaten, she reveals that the master of Harvey Troupe did not die in an accident, she killed him.\n
        -   Estelle tries to reason with Renne. Facing Estelle makes Renne confused, which she has not experienced for a long time.
            Renne refuses to talk to Estelle and calls Pater-Mater to fight the party. Renne reveals that her parents left her
            bad strangers and promised to come back for her but they never did. Renne had seen many other children died in her
            childhood. It was thanks to Loewe and Joshua came to rescue her that she\'s now still alive and is an enforcer.\n
        -   After Estelle fails to help Renne, she is more determined to not giving up on Renne.\n
        -   While professor Russell is analyzing the data from the towers, the Liber Ark suddenly appears. He forces the Arseille to
            land immediately. His fear becomes true when the Liber Ark causes the Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon across the entire Liberl.
            Unfortunately for Bobcat, it was crashed on the top of Liber Ark.\n\n
        Chapter 8: The Land of Chaos\n
        -   The Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon causes a major panic. Your party splits off to handle the situation.\n
        -   Estelle is assigned to give anti-Gospel devices to Bracer Guild branches to recover communication.\n
        -   In Ruan, Gilbert and several red jaegars attacks Jenis Academy to find Kloe. They were defeated by many bracers.\n
        -   After delivering the last device, Ouroboros attacks Grancel directly. Even Duke Dunan tries his best to protect
            Queen Alicia and Kloe from Enforcers but they fail. Even when the party arrives to rescue, they can\'t defeat 4
            enforcers at the same time. During the dire situation, Colonel Richard leads the Intelligence Division to attack
            red jaegars and protect Grancel. The purpose of the whole invasion is just for fun, so the enforcers leave.\n
        -   Not long after the invasion, Erebonia army is at the north of Haken Gate and is preparing to cross the border.
            Their reason is because the phenomenon affects south Erebonia as well. Also, Erebonians think the Liber Ark is
            Liberl\'s weapon to get revenge for the Hundred Days War. The man who leads the Erebonia army at the gate is Olivier.\n
        -   Thanks to a secret deal between Olivier and Cassius, also the effort of Claudia von Auslese, Olivier manages to hold
            the advance of the army temporary.\n
        -   Immediately after that, Olivier and Mueller join our party to go on board on the Arseille to stop the phenomenon.\n\n
        Finale: Trails in the Sky\n
        -   The Arseille suffers damage and requires time to repair after it manages to land on the Liber Ark.\n
        -   The party explores the area and finds Josette. Josette says that her brothers and the entire crew got captured and
            she wants to save them. They save the crews who are captured in the Glorious.\n
        -   After that, the Capua is trying to fix the Bobcat while supporting the party to end the phenomenon.\n
        -   The party reaches a massive tower called Axis Pillar. The enforcers are guarding it at several floors.\n
        -   Bleublanc is defeated first but he promises this is just the beginning.\n
        -   Walter reveals that Zin was the chosen successor but Walter did not want to fight him for the position because he
            was sure Zin would allow him to win. Zin informs Walter that their master was already dying of a terminal illness.
            Zin and Walter exchange the last blow, Walter faints while Zin remains standing.\n
        -   Luciola tells Schera that she was in love with the master of the Troupe, but he planned to sell the circus and carried
            his debt alone. She was snapped and pushed him off a cliff so he would never leave her. She realizes her darkness so
            she left Schera to protect her. She tries to commit suicide by leaping from Axis Pillar. Schera uses her whip to
            grab Luciola\'s arm but she cut the whip and falls. Luciola\'s fate remains unknown. Before Luciola falls, she reveals
            that she participates in the Gospel Plan in order to see Schera one more time and ensure that she was happy in her new life.\n
        -   Renne and Pater-Mater lost the fight. Estelle tries to reason with Renne again but Renne refuses everything she says.
            Renne reasons that Estelle knows nothing about her so she has no right to convince her. Estelle loves Renne and wants
            to save Renne, because of that, Estelle has to slap Renne and tells her off for not considering the others she has hurt.
            Renne says that Estelle is the same with those adults who hurt Renne. Estelle hugs Renne and ask her to listen to her heart.
            Renne does not dislike the feeling of being hugged but her stubbornness makes her refuse Estelle again. But this time, Renne
            says she wants to be alone and thinks. She warns that Loewe is waiting for them then flies away.\n
        -   Before the fight, Loewe wanrs them that his full power surpass S-Ranked bracer and even a Anguis of Ouroboros. Estelle
            says it does not matter because she has to stop a Weissmann from obtaining Aureole and prevent a war. Joshua offers a
            one-to-one fight against Loewe. Loewe desires to test humanity\'s potential to learn if Karin\'s sacrifice was
            worth it. Joshua disaarms Loewe with a final attack. Loewe declares that he has found his answer and has no reason to
            stay with Ouroboros anymore, and hints to become a bracer like he used to wish.\n
        -   Weissmann suddenly appears and deals a severe damage to Loewe. Joshua is controlled by Weissmann again.\n
        -   When the party is ready to go to the top, several dragons attacked them. But thanks to everyone who stays in
            the Areseille and the Capuas to hold the dragons back, the party moves on to the final fight.\n
        -   Weismann reveals the truth about the Liber Ark. Aidios mankind the Sept-Terrion. Seven groups used their power to
            create their perfect society. The Liber Ark was a floating paradise, allowing them to pursue anything they want.
            Aurole provided the citizens anything they desired, which later led to a kind of moral decay with all sorts of crime
            occurring, people exhibiting addiction-like symptoms to the miracle they had become accustomed to and suicides increasing.
            Aureole cared nothing for this and kept providing the miracles.\n
        -   Weissmann asks if sealing the Aureole was the right decision. With the rise of orbal technologies which makes
            life easier. The humanity is doomed to repeat the same mistakes. His ambition and gola of the Gospel Plan is to
            use the Ring\'s power to evolve humanity so people have the control not to be overcome by adversity or emotions
            and the intelligence to always make the correct decision. This is the mission he has been entrusted with as one
            of the Anguis in the service of the Grandmaster of Ouroboros.\n
        -   As they fight, Joshua suddenly strikes Weissmann. It was thanks to Kevin who modifies the Stigma to make it
            self-destruct if a particular command was given.\n
        -   Weissmann changes his plan and begins the final phase of the Gospel Plan immediately. He leaps into the center
            of Aureole and transforms into Angel Weissmann. Weissmann overwhelms the whole party but Loewe manages to come
            and attack him. Loewe asks what rol did Weissmann play in the Hamel tragedy. Weissmann reveals that he
            whispered to a certain noble and introduce them some jaegers.\n
        -   Loewe has his suspicion for a long time ago so he was calm. Loewe later uses the sword which was a gift from
            the Grandmaster to cut down Weissman\'s Sept-Terrion barrier that grants absolute dominion over Space. However,
            Loewe was thrown back and suffers a severe injure. The party takes the chance to defeat Weissmann.\n
        -   After Weissmann is defeated, he escapes with the Aureole. But Kevin Graham has been waiting for him. Kevin
            reveals that he is Dominion number V, the Heretic killer. Kevin shoots Weissmann with an arrow made of a part pf
            Salt Pale tree and kills him. Campanella appears to retrieve Weissmann\'s staff and leave without bothering about his dead.\n
        -   Loewe is dying there is nothing the party can do, no matter how much Joshua begs him not to go, leaving him alone just like
            when Karin died. Loewe asks Joshua to live and asks Estelle to take care of him. The Liber Ark starts collapsing
            after Loewe dies, but Joshua is unable to leave him. Estelle reminds him what Loewe just said and whatever happens
            next, they\'ll face it together. Unable to take Loewe\'s body with him, Joshua picks up his sword and flees with the rest.\n
        -   Everyone is able to escape on Arseille and Bobcat but because Joshua and Estelle were late and the path collapesed, they
            are ready to die and fall from the sky. Cassius rides on Ragnard and saves both of them.\n\n
        Epilogue\n
        -   Estelle and Joshua visit Karin\'s grave. Joshua lays Kernviter (Loewe\'s sword) next to her grave.\n
        -   They are now leaving Liberl to find Renne and investigate Ouroboros\'s next move.\n </string>

    <string name="title_3rd_Summary">
        Trails in the Sky The 3rd is the third installment of the Trails series and the final installment of Liberl arc.\n\n
        Prologue\n
        -   Kevin was asked to come to Grancel\'s Cathedral to look at an artifact coming from the Liber Arc, the Recluse Cube.
            While negotiating with Erika Russell about how this artifact should be handled,
            Ries Argent comes to join the conversation. In the end, it was decided that Kevin will hold the artifact.\n
        -   The artifact suddenly activated later that night and pulls Kevin, Ries, and Gilbert into an unknown dimension.\n\n
        Chapter 1: Phantasma\n
        -   Kevin and Ries begin their investigation in the Hermit\'s Garden. They find a way to explore outside the Garden
            by using the Cube. The one who tells them is a mystery female voice that appears and disappears randomly.\n
        -   They find the place they are at is very strange and dangerous due to the appearance of demons that are mentioned
            in the Testament of Septian Church.\n
        -   During their investigation, they find a strange stone that seals a person inside. The first one they meet is Tita Russell.\n
        -   Together with Tita, they find the Arseille. According to Tita, the orbal technology is not working at all.\n
        -   They find Captain Julia Schwarz inside a stone, similar to Tita.\n
        -   A masked man name Schwarzritter proclaims himself to be a servant of the lord of this dimension, Phantasma.\n\n
        Chapter 2: The Otherworldly Capital\n
        -   Julia questions how the masked man knows Ries\' older sister, Rufina. Ries reveals that Rufina was a knight
            of the Gralsritter who died during a mission five years ago.\n
        -   In the second plane of Phantasma, it takes shape of the whole Grancel. However, it is just an empty city.\n
        -   The party find Mueller Vander, Josette Capua, Joshua Bright in stones and Gilbert in actual person.\n
        -   The Lord of Phantasma later appears in front of everyone while holding the stone of princess Klaudia. He promises
            to return the stone if they overcome the trial.\n
        -   The party wins the fight and obtain the stone of princess Klaudia. The Lord taunts Kevin to figure out his trick.\n\n
        Chapter 3: Golden Road, Silver Road\n
        -   Klaudia is released with her falcon Sieg from the sealing stone.\n
        -   On the third plane, the path splits into two: a silver road and a golden road. The party is split and each goes
            to explore the roads. Kevin and Ries lead each team of four. Kevin takes the golden road and Ries takes the silver road.\n
        -   In the road, Kevin and Ries find items that are connected to Rufina: The Aion Bow and the Sulvahn. At the end of each
            road, they have to fight their doppelganger. Each team receives a sealing stone after defeating it.\n
        -   Schwarzritter congratulates them at the cross road. He gives information about a ghostly woman that has been
            helping them. He calls her the hermit and mentions that she is the master of the Hermit\'s Garden. However, because
            of the Lord, she loses most of her power and there are little things she can do.\n
        Chapter 4: The Dark Stigma\n
        -   The two new members released from the stones are Olivert Reisei Arnor and Zin Vathek.\n
        -   Olivert believes that the Lord is related to Kevin in some manner. During the discussion, Kevin\'s attitude upsets
            Ries, so she wishes to take a break and remains in the garden. Kevin talks to her in private out of concern. Ries is
            upset because of Kevin\'s acting friendly with everyone while keeping her and them out of the loop.\n
        -   Joshua later talks to him to say thank you despite Kevin being a double face in several cases in SC. He offers
            to be Kevin\'s right hand for the time being, and Kevin accepts.\n
        -   The fourth plane takes place in the training camp Le Locle.\n
        -   The party frees Anelace Elfead, Scherazard Harvey, and Agate Crosner during the exploration.\n
        -   When the party is ready to move to the next location after the portal opens, a devil uses Evil Eye curse to
            bind the whole team. Ries appears to protects the team, but the devil is too strong. When it almost kills Ries,
            Kevin releases his insignia and kills the devil.\n
        -   The Lord appears to give the party another stone. The next member is Estelle Bright. However, Estelle notices
            Kevin\'s pale face, and he passes out due to exhaustion.\n\n
        Chapter 5: Labyrinth of Shadows and Light\n
        -   Ries confirms that the power Kevin used against the demon is the true Stigma. Ries becomes team leader temporarily.\n
        -   The new members are ex-Colonel Richard and Renne.\n
        -   Renne is panic and upset after she sees Joshua and Estelle. It was because they were trying to look for her over
            the past several months. The conversation gets worse when Ries is upset with Renne\'s selfishness, but Tita manages
            to settle down. Renne later decides to help the team because she wants to learn why she ends up in Phantasma.\n
        -   Thanks to Renne, the party learns more about the nature of Phantasma.\n
        -   The final sealing stone the party receives is Celeste D. Auslese, the ancestor of Klaudia.\n\n
        Chapter 6: The Guardians\' Trials\n
        -   Celeste explains that she is just a copy of the real person, an A.I.. Her task was to help the real one to
            seal Aureole back in the Dark Ages. The Phantasma belongs to Aureole. When Ouroboros removed the Aureole,
            it should have been slowly dissappearing peacefully but the Lord appeared to take over the Phantasma.\n
        -   The party faces with several trials, battling against other characters who are known in the past 2 games.\n
        -   The final trial is to defeat, Scharzritter, who turns out to be Loewe. When he is fading away, Joshua informs
            him that Joshua has placed his sword next to Karin\'s grave, and Joshua is ready to move on and become stronger.
            Loewe is satisfied and finally rests in peace.\n
        -   The final place is the Aster House, where Kevin, Ries, and Rufina grew up together.\n\n
        Chapter 7: The Distant Flames\n
        -   In the chapel, Kevin reveals the truth behind Rufina\'s dead. A group of jaegers hired by an unknown party raided
            the Aster House. Kevin managed to silently eliminate the enemies, but Ries was held hostage under the Chapel.
            While reaching the basement, Kevin had the flashback about the tragic past of his mother trying to commit a double-suicide with
            Kevin because his father abandoned both of them. The jaeger was alarmed when he saw Kevin so he dropped Ries down
            and ran to grab the artifact in the basement: the Spear of Loa that transforms its wielder into a monster. Kevin
            fought the beast but he was overwhelmed. His stigma activated when the beast tried to kill Ries. After the beast was
            killed, he couldn\'t control his bloodlust and ended up killing Rufina who tried to calm him down.\n
        -   Kevin accepts to receive punishment under Ries\' hand, but she is furious because Kevin kept hiding the secret
            and suffering all alone while it was not his fault.\n
        -   The Lord appears and asks Kevin about his identity. Kevin points out the Lord is the false Rufina, who was created
            by Kevin\'s mind. The Lord later causes a rift to send Ries to an abyss. Kevin jumps down before the rift is shut.\n
        -   The abyss, the seventh plane, is resembles to Gehenna. Kevin and Ries work together to escape Gehnna.\n
        -   On their way to the top, they battle against demons who represent Kevin\'s nightmare: a flesh-eating child whom
            Kevin failed to save, Bishop Owen who was responsible for the attack of the Aster House, Kevin\'s mother.\n
        -   They face Georg at the door to escape Genhenna. After Georg is defeated, the gate is still remained shut.
            A group of tough winged devils chasing Gilbert who is heading to their way. Thankfully, the rest of the party, with
            the help of Celeste, manages to open the path to Gehenna and rescue them all.\n\n
        Finale: The Future We Dream Of\n
        -   In order to settle down everything, the team decides to take down Rufina. Celeste makes Arseille functional to
            take everyone to Rufina\'s location. However, a small group of dragons attacking the Arseille, so Gilbert uses
            hid G-Apache to distract them. Thanks to his help, the team arrives at Phantasmagoria.\n
        -   It is revealed that the Lord is actually a copy of his Stigma known as Anima.\n
        -   After Anima is defeated, it takes the form of Rufina again. This time, the real Rufina talks to them, she asks
            Kevin to kill her fast to prevent the Lord from reviving. Kevin is hesitated but Ries is with him, together, they
            bid their final farewells to Rufina and shoot her with Kevin\'s crossbow.\n
        -   The planes start to collapse after Anima\'s destruction, everyone starts leaving one after another. Even Gilbert
            manages to escape before the plane gone.\n
        -   Kevin has finally overcome his past, he gets rid of his Heretic\'s Hunter title and thinks about a new name for the new him.\n
    </string>

    <string name="country_liberl_summary">The Liberl Kingdom is located in southwestern Zemuria. Its mainland is
        bordered to the south by the Thetis Sea and to the west by an unnamed ocean; to the north by Erebonia;
        and to the east by Calvard. Its crest is a white falcon.\n
        The name Liberl comes from the Liber Ark, the floating city governed by Sept-terion Aureole during
        the ancient time of Zemuria.\n\n
        The collapse of Liber Ark:\n
        -   The Liber Ark is a floating island city that brings prosperity to its citizens.\n
        -   However, over time, the reliance on the Aureole led to a decline in morals and ethics.\n
        -   As the result, madness and despair were spread all over the population.\n
        -   Celeste D von Auslese decided to end their reliance on the Aureole.\n
        -   However, Aureole resisted and treated them as enemies to prevent Liber Ark\'s destruction.\n
        -   Celeste D von Auslese succeeded in sealing both Aureole and Liber Ark in a different dimension.\n
        -   Celeste established the Liberl Kingdom in approzimately S.1\n\n
        The modern era:\n
        -   The clash between aristocrats and commoners reached climax after 100 years since the founded day.\n
        -   Princess Cecilia was responsible for abolishing the difference in classes in Liberl.\n
        -   Aristocracy still exists in a very small portion and uncommon in Liberl nowadays.\n\n
        Hundred Days War:\n
        -   In spring S.1192, Imperial Army of Erebonia started invading Liberl.\n
        -   Liberl was losing fast due to Imperial Army\'s blitz strategy.\n
        -   Liberl turned the table with the large scale counter-attack by using newly-developed patrol ships.\n
        -   In S.1193, a peace treaty was signed by Liberl and Erebonia, which marks the end of the Hundred Days War.\n
        (Warning: the followings are top secret international information that must not be revealed to the public)\n
        -   The cause of war: a massacre at night of Hamel village of Erebonia, which was located near
            the border between two countries.\n
        -   There was sight of perpetrators wearing Liberl Army uniform and using Liber\'s weapons.\n
        -   The Hamel incident is buried to the darkness because there was no survivor and there\'s possibly
            a third party that caused the massacre.\n
        -   It was revealed by Anguis III of Ouroboros, Georg Weissmann that he was the one suggested
            to an unknown party to cause the Hamel incident.\n\n
        Coup d\'etat:\n
        -   In S.1202, Colonel Alan Richard of the Royal Army\'s Intelligence Division attempted a coup.\n
        -   He was stopped by a joint force between the Royal Guardsmen, the Bracer Guild, ZCF, and princess Claudia.\n
        -   The true perpetrator was Georg Weissmann of the Society.\n
        -   The coup was prevented, however, the Gospel Plan of the Society was a success, which later led to the
            Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon.\n\n
        Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon:\n
        -   In S.1203, a country-wide Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon occurred, which disabled all orbal devices and caused
            a mass panic.\n
        -   The phenomenon also affected south of Erebonia, which caused the Imperial Army almost breached the
            Hanken Gate again.\n
        -   Thanks to Princess Klaudia of Liberl, the bracers and Prince Olivier of Erebonia,
            the Imperial Army halted their
            advancement temporarily and allowed Liberl Army and Bracers some time to stop the phenomenon.\n
        -   Liber Ark collapsed and the phenomenon was prevented.\n
        -   S-rank bracer Cassius Bright retired and returned to his previous position as commander of Royal Army
            of Liberl.\n
        Interntional event:\n
        -   Before the Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon, Queen Alicia managed to host a Non-Aggression Pact between Liberl,
            Erebonia, and Calvard.\n
    </string>
    <string name="country_calvard_summary">The Republic of Calvard is located in the western Zemuria. It is \n
        bordered to the southwest by Liberl, to the west by Erebonia and Crossbell; to the northwest by \n
        Remiferia; and to the east by Ored.\n\n
        It was founded in S.1090 and is famous for its immigration policy that allows people from the East to live
        in Calvard.\n\n
        Republican revolution:\n
        -   Around S.1100, the country was struck with a financial disaster.\n
        -   Merchants from East Zemuria financially supported the revolution to overthrow the ruling monarchy.\n
        -   In S.1187, the passenger ship Eterna sank in Calvardian waters, resulted the dead of Crown Prince
            Judis von Auslese and his wife.\n\n
        Hundred Days War:\n
        -   During the war, Calvard was unable to quickly support its neighbor country, Liberl, against Erebonia\'s
            blitz strategy.\n
        Relationship with Erebonia:\n
        -   Their relationship gets worse after the completion of the orbal railgun cannons at Garrelia Fortress, located
            at easternmost border of Erebonia.\n
        -   Even after the successful Non-Aggression Pact hosted in Liberl, their relationship is still far from good.\n\n
        </string>
    <string name="country_erebonia_summary">The Erebonia Empire is located in western Zemuria. It is bordered to
        the east by Calvard and to the south by Liberl.\n\n
        War of the Lions:\n
        -   The death of emperor Valius V in S.947 and the assassination of his son, the fourth prince Orthos
            seizes power in a military coupe of Heimdallr and declares himself the new emeperor.\n
        -   Orthos declares to purge anyone who dares to oppose him which accelerate the civil war.\n
        -   Prince Dreichels started raising an army and departs from Nord Highlands, hoping to end the war and to
            bring back the peace of Erebonians.\n
        -   Dreichels brought the end to Orthos\' tyranny and became the new emperor of Erebonia.\n\n
        Border disputes:\n
        -   Both Erebonia and Calvard grew rapidly and became two most powerful nations in Zemuria.\n
        -   Their growths also means the expansion of territories.\n
        -   The territory that both sides try to get is later established as Crossbell State.\n\n
        Hundred Days War:\n
        -   The lost of Hamel led Erebonia to declare war on Liberl Kingdom.\n
        -   Thanks to the manpower and blitz strategy, they advanced extremely fast and Liberl was likely to lose at any time.\n
        -   Liberl counter attacked with patrol ships and pushed Imperial Army out of the country.\n
        -   Erebonia signed the peace treaty and apologized to Liberl.\n
        -   Gilliath Osborne was promoted to chancellor of blood and iron.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="country_crossbell_summary">Crossbell State, formerly known as Corssbell Province, is a lanlocked,
        self-governing demilitarised buffer state located in wester Zemuria. It is bordered by Erebonia to the west and
        by Calvard to the east.\n\n
        There are a lot of mysteries surrounding Crossbell dated back to the Dark Ages. Specifically the ancient bells
        that are located in several location in Crossbell States.\n
        The state has a very complex situation. Erebonia and Calvard have been hostile to each other for the ownership of
        Crossbell province. Crossbell State was established in S.1137I to prevent the bloodshed between them. In a sense,
        some can say it is a share property of both Erebonia and Calvard.\n
        In the present, Crossbell State is growing extremely fast due to its location allows trades between two super nations
        Erebonia and Calvard</string>
    <string name="location_hamel_summary">WARNING: any information about Hamel must not be disclosed to the public and any unrelated party. The truth about Hamel can cause another huge international incident.\n\n
        Hamel was a small village in Erebonia Empire. It was located near the border between Erebonia and Liberl.\n
        One night, an unknown armed group massacred the village and left no one survive. According to Erebonia, they found evidences that led them to believe Liberl army was that group.\n
        After the incident is the Hundred Days War. It is unknown what Erebonia, or specifically, chancellor Gilliath Osborn found to make them agree to ceasefire and apologize to Liberl.
        The man who indirectly cause the incident is Anguis III of the Society, Georg Weissmann. However, he was killed by the a Dominion for his sins before we could find out more about the massacre.\n\n
        In the incident, however, there were 2 residents of Hamel survived the massacre:\n
        -   Leonhardt, enforcer No. 2 of the Society, known as Bladelord. He suffered a fatal wound by Georg Weissmann and died at Liber Arc.\n
        -   Joshua Bright, enforcer No. 12 of the Society, known as Black Fang. After the massacre, somehow Joshua and Leonhardt were recruited by Georg himself and became enforcers.
        Joshua has discarded his connection to the Society and becomes Bracer.\n\n
        In the record, Joshua Bright is the only survivor of the incident.
    </string>

    <string name="TL_txtviewIntro">The Zemuria continent follows the Septian Calendar
        to the present day.\n
        Note that the timeline in this guide is incomplete. It only shows the major events that are
        considered necessary and related for Liberl\'s bracers.\n
        The history is divided into 3 eras:\n
        1. After the Septian Calendar (1~500AS).\n
        2. After the Dark Ages (500~1100AD).\n
        3. After the Orbal Revolution (1150AR~).\n
    </string>
    <string name="TL_txtview2">Before the Septian Calendar is the era which is told that Gods fought and
        mutually killed each other after a 100 days struggle.\n
        The Sky Goddess, Aidios, gave humanity the Sept-Terrion, seven sacred treasures which
        granted dominion over the land, skies, and seas. They were eventually separated dividing humanity
        to pursue the respective ideals. </string>
    <string name="TL_year1">The Great Collapese brought the end of the ancient Zemurian civilization.\n
        Celeste D. Auslese sealed the Aureole in another dimension with the floating city, Liber Ark.
        Liberl Kingdom was founded below after.\n
        Around 1 - 500AS, Erebonia Empire was founded.
    </string>
    <string name="TL_year82">The Grancel Cathedral was built in the kingdom\'s capital.</string>
    <string name="TL_year200">The Order of the Gralsritter was founded.</string>
    <string name="TL_year_B500">The Dark Ages began.</string>
    <string name="TL_year_A500">The Septian Church appeared as Aidios religion, ending the Dark Ages.</string>
    <string name="TL_year1100">Liberl\'s decree of nobility has been abolished.\n
        The Calvard Republic was born.</string>
    <string name="TL_year1150">The Orbal Revolution started after Professor C.Epstein invented
        the first orbment.\n Bracer Guild was founded.</string>
    <string name="TL_year1162">Princess Alicia II inherited the throne at the age of 20 after
        king Edgar III\'s death.</string>
    <string name="TL_year1192w">WARNING: Any information about Hamel Village is international top secret.
        Bracers must not reveal this information to any unrelated party to prevent the continuation of
        the Hundred Days War.\n
    </string>
    <string name="TL_year1192">Tragedy occurred at Hamel Village, which was near the border between
        Erebonia Empire and Liberl Kingdom. The Hundred Days War started during spring after.\n
        The Imperial Army of Erebonia declared war and immediately attacked Liberl.\n
        2 months later, Albert Russell developed military patrolships. This allowed Liberl to
        counter attacked the Imperial Army.\n
        The ceasefire was agreed between Liberl and Erebonia. The Hamel incident was buried in the darkness.\n
        The Hamel incident led Leonhardt and Joshua to join the Ouroboros.
    </string>
    <string name="TL_year1196">Renne Haywworth was abducted in Calvard Republic.
        Later rescued by Ouroboros. Renne joined Ouroboros.</string>
    <string name="TL_year1201">The Liberl Intelligence Division was established.</string>
    <string name="TL_year1202">Erebonian Bracer Guilds were attacked.\n
        Cassius Bright was requested to solve the incident.\n
        Liberlian airship, Linde, was attacked by Sky Bandit and gone missing.\n
        Junior bracers Estelle and Joshua Bright began their adventure in Liberl.\n
        The 60th annual Queen\'s Birthday.\n
        A non-aggression pact was signed in Liberl, between Liberl, Calvard, and Erebonia.</string>
    <string name="TL_year1203">The Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon caused nationwide panic in Liberl.\n
        Erebonia Empire army was in the verge of invading Liberl again because
        the phenomenon affected south Erebonia.\n
        Kevin Graham and Ries Argent recovered an ancient artifact from the collapsed Liber Ark.</string>

    <string name="bracer_guild_description">Bracer Guild is an international non-governmental organisation
        acting to keep the peace and protect civilians. Its members are called bracers.\n
        Due to its international and neutral nature, it often mediates between disputing powers from small to
        large scale. Such as the Hundred Days War, the coup in Liberl, and the Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon.
        However, at the same time, Bracer Guild\'s activities can be severely limited for its Guild Code.\n\n
        Guild Code contains laws that bracer guild and all bracers must follow. Simply put, bracers are not allowed
        to involve and interfere in any nation\'s dispute when no harm is likely to happen to civilians.\n
        However, the loophole in the Guild Code can be used to allow Bracers to act immediately. During the coup, a
        citizen\'s request can allow Bracer Guild to act immediately to protect citizens from harm.</string>
    <string name="septian_church_description">The Septian Church is a monotheistic religion formed around the Goddess
        of the Sky known as Aidios. The High Seat of the Septian Church is established in Arteria.\n\n
        The first appearance of the Church is said to have occurred approximately S.500, which marked the end of
        the Dark Age.\n
        However, it is also possible that the Church has existed since before the Great Collapse,
        and it has been active in the public since after the Great Collapse.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="gralsritter_description">The Gralsritter is an order within the Septian Church, responsible
        for the investigation and retrieval of ancient Zemurian artifacts.\n\n
        There are 6 principles Gralsritter must follow:\n
        -   Offer your soul to Goddess and your body to Her church.\n
        -   Protect the Sacraments.\n
        -   Swear loyalty to the Holy Father.\n
        -   Carry out your duties with dignity.\n
        -   Protect the peace and order of the three worlds.\n
        -   Heretics must be eliminated.\n\n
        Knight is a promoted class among the Gralsritter of the Septian Church. They are also tasked to
        support the Dominion they have been assigned to.\n\n
        Squire is a base class among the Gralsritter of the Septian Church.</string>
    <string name="dominion_description">Dominion has 12 special knights among the Gralsritter and acts as
        the organization leaders. The Dominion have been active for about a thousand years. A manifestation
        of a Stigma is required in order to be promoted to the rank of Dominion.\n</string>
    <string name="epstein_foundation_description">Epstein Foundation is dedicated to spread orbal technologies
        across Zemuria. It was found by the disciples of C.Epstein (father of orbal technology) after his death.\n
        The Epstein Foundation researches and manufactures orbments, specialising in information processing and
        communication.</string>
    <string name="zcf_description">Zeiss Central Factory (ZCF) is an orbment research facility located in Liberl.\n
        Initially, Albert Russell (a disciple of C.Epstein) formed a partnership with Zeiss Clockmaker\'s Union.\n
        Together, they establish the Zeiss Engineering Factory in S.1157 and created orbment outside of
        Epstein Foundation.\n
        In S.1160, King Edgar III of Liberl visited the factory and decided to donate a large amount of
        money to further its research. Thanks to King Edgar III, orbments began to spread like wildfire
        across the kingdom, bringing prosperity to the people of Liberl.\n
        In S.1173, Zeiss Engineering Factory is renamed to Zeiss Central Factory.\n
        In S.1182, Albert Russell resigned from his position as Factory Chief.\n
        In S.1190, ZCF publicly announced the Orbal Network, a joint venture between ZCF and the
        Epstein Foundation.</string>
    <string name="ouroboros_description">Ouroboros, also known as the Society, is a mysterious organization
        that operates from the shadows in Zemuria.\n
        With its access to powerful, talented agents, and the latest technological advances that surpass any
        cutting edge technologies in Zemuria, it is involved in many major incidents that occur in Zemuria.\n
        It is unknown when Ouroboros was founded. The earliest record date back to S.1192, prior the Hundred
        Days War, but it is generally assumed that the Society has existed far longer than that.\n\n
        Gospel Plan:\n
        -   Their first publicly involvement is the coup led by Alan Richard in Liberl. The coup was a part of the
        Gospel Plan, that later caused the Liber Arc from the Dark Ages to reappeared in Liberl which caused
        Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon.\n
        -   The main objective of the Gospel Plan was to obtain Aureole, the Sept-Terrion
        of Space that controls the Liber Arc.\n
        -   The plan was guided by the third Anguis of the Society, Georg Weissmann.\n
        -   Georg Weissmann revealed that he was the mastermind that indirectly caused the Hundred Days War.\n\n
        In Trails in the Sky: The 3rd, it was revealed in the last secret door that Gospel Plan was just the first
        phase of Orpheus Final Plan, the main plan of the Society. After the Liber Arc incident, the Society is
        ready for the second phase, the Phantasmal Blaze Plan.\n\n
        Hierarchy:\n
        -   Grandmaster\n
        -   Anguis I, Campanella\n
        -   Anguis II - VII\n
        -   Enforcers\n
        -   Jaegers (mainly Red Constellation)
    </string>
    <string name="intelligence_divison_liberl_description">The division was formed per suggestion of Colonel Alan Richard
        to Queen Alicia von Auslese II. Richard had Captain Kanone Amalthea re-assigned to his aide-de-camp.\n
        The division was responsible for the coup before the Queen\'s birthday anniversary and several incidents across
        the nation few months back: the Capua Sky bandits, the scandal of mayor Morris Dalmore,
        the kidnap of Professor Albert Russell, the false accusation toward Royal Guards, and the secret house-arrest of
        princess Klaudia von Auslese.\n\n
        It was revealed at the end of Sora no Kiseki FC that Colonel Richard was also under the influence of Georg Weissmann
        of the society, similar to the ringleaders of aforementioned incidents.\n\n
        The nature of the coup was not out of malice, however Colonel Alan Richard has endangered many people for his plan. After
        he was freed from Georg Weissmann\'s influence, he accepted to be in prison.\n\n
        However, Captain Kanone Amalthea and several men from the division managed to escape after the coup. They planned to
        sabotage Grancel a few months later, demanding Alan Richard to be released. Their plan was failed thanks to the
        assistance of Father Kevin Graham from the Septian Church. After the remains were arrested, Cassius Bright let Alan met
        Kanone to let her know that Alan has accepted the outcome so she doesn\'t have to fight anymore.\n\n
        During the direct attack from the Society to Grancel, it was all thanks to commander Cassius Bright, who has predicted
        such possibility, to temporary relieve Alan Richard and the whole division to protect the capital.\n\n
        After their achievement in protecting Grancel, the division was disbanded. All members were allocated to different
        division. Only Alan Richard and Kanone Amalthea retired and fonded R &amp; A Research.
    </string>
    <string name="red_constellation_description">Red Constellation is one of the strongest Jaegar corps in Zemuria.\n
        Their origins date back to the Dark Ages where they began as Orlando\'s Berserkers, a warrior clan.\n\n
        In Sora no Kiseki, they were known as red Jaegar corp of the Society.
    </string>

    <string name="char_agate">
        Agate Crosner, known as the Heavy Blade, is a bracer of Liberl.\n
        He was born in Ravennue Village in S.1178. He lived happily with his younger sister, Mischa, until the
            Hundred Days War struck in S.1192.\n\n
        During the war, Mischa attempted to retrieve her birthday gift for Agate inside their burning house, which
            led to her dead. Agate had been suffered with anger and self-hatred since then.\n
        He confronted mayor Maybelle\'s father house because the mayor abandoned the village during the Erebonia\'s attack.
            Maybelle at that time did not understand the situation but seeing her father was insulted made her slap Agate.
            But Agate ignored her and later punch her father then left.\n\n
        After a period of time, he left the village and wandered around until he stopped at Ruan and became the leader of
            the Ravens, a local port gang. During his criminal period, he met Cassius Bright who later turned him into a Bracer
            and left the Ravens.\n\n
        Despite working as bracer to help people, Agate was still suffered from his sister\'s dead. He left a bad impression
            for Estelle and Joshua for his attitude toward junior Bracers who try to handle serious situations.\n\n
        During FC, he had been pursuing the men in black, the division intelligence, for a long time. He confronted Lt. Lorence and
            crossed his sword with Lorence. Lorence pointed out Agate\'s was swinging his blade aimlessly without a clear goal
            made Agate was angrier.\n
        When Prof. Albert was being kidnapped by the Intelligence Division members, Tita tried to save his grandfather but
            her weapon caused a member panic that he shot a very dangerous poison at her. Agate jumped out and got hit by
            the poison which almost killed him. Luckily, Estelle team managed to find the cure and saved him. During his recover,
            he woke up at night and mistook Tita was his sister, Mischa. When Tita asked him who Mischa was, he told her Mischa was
            his sister but he lied about her dead. After prof. Albert was rescued, Agate, prof. Albert and Tita split with
            the Brights so the Brights can inform the Queen about the coup while Agate hid prof. Albert and Tita away.\n\n
        During SC, his village was set afire by a dragon under manipulation of George Weissmann. To make it worse, Lorence aka
            Loewe was with the dragon angered Agate which made Agate chased after them alone. Agate was no match against Loewe and was
            almost got killed by him, but Tita jumped out and did everything to save him. Agate was saved but he was heavily injured
            so Estelle team rushed him back to his house in the village. The team also learnt about his past later after the fight.
            Tita decided to stay back to take care of Agate. Later that night, Agate had a conversation with Tita. Thanks to Tita,
            Agate managed to remove the curse of self-hatred for all these years.\n\n
        Sometime before the 3rd, Agate visited Tita\'s house to have a dinner. However, Tita\'s mother, Erika Russell, doesn\'t
            like him because he left the impression of being a delinquent and a punk.
    </string>

    <string name="char_alan">
        Alan Richard, the Dinvine Blade\'s Successor, the Ex-Colonel of Liberl, the co-founder of RA Research.\n\n
        He was an extraordinary talent officer who supported Cassius Bright during the Hundred Days War. After Colonel
            Bright\'s retirement, he was feared of the weakening Liberl. So he founded the Intelligence Division to
            reinforce his country\'s strength. He was manipulated by Georg Weissmann, and later begin his coup plot.\n\n
        He was publicly known as the hero who solved the country\'s problems, including all events happened during FC.
            He arranged a house arrest of Queen Alicia and Princess Klaudia. However, his plan was foiled by the Bracer
            Guild, led by Estelle and Joshua Bright with their companions. He realized his mistake and accepted his prison
            time. Months later, Cassius recognized his genuine patriotism, as the result, he and the rest of Intelligence
            Division had the chance to redeem themselves by protecting Grancel during the Scoeity direct attack.\n\n
        Despite everyone\'s wish to have him remain in the military, Richard retired and found RA Research with Kanone Amalthea
            to continue his patriotism in a different way.

    </string>

    <string name="char_albert">
        Albert Russell is a famous orbal engineer workin at the ZFC. He is a student of Epstein and is known as
            the "Father of the Orbal Revolution".\n\n
        He is an eccentric researcher whose passion for technology has no end. He lives together with his dear
            granddaughter Tita.\n\n
        In FC, he was kidnapped by the Intelligence Division due to his talent.\n\n
        At the end of FC and during SC, his genius mind helped the Liberl greatly.
    </string>

    <string name="char_alba_weissmann">
        Alba, real name is Georg Weissmann, known as The Faceless, the former third Anguis of the Society. He was a
            bishop of the Septian Church until he joined the Society for his own interest.\n\n
        He was the mastermind behind the every incident in FC and SC. He also instigated the Hundred Days War.\n\n
        His homeland was North Ambria. At the age of 13, the Pillar of Salt hit his homeland and killed both of his parents.
            He was pursuing to re-create the Stigma to create superhumans. His actions were against the wish of the Septian Church.\n\n
        He is an evil, manipulative person who is willing to do anything to  fulfill his plan. He was killed by Kevin Graham by the
            same Pillar of Salt that killed his parents. Due to his nature, no one, even the Society, mourned for his dead.

    </string>

    <string name="char_alicia">
        Alicia von Auslese, known as Alicia II, is the queen of Liberl.\n
        During FC, Lorence said she had no right to advise him what to do, because she was one of those who gave up on
            bringing the justice for the victims of Hamel Village. However, no one can criticize her action, even Lorence,
            because queen Alicia did what a ruler must do to protect her country.\n
        During SC, Joshua accepted her apology for the Tragedy of Hamel Village.
    </string>

    <string name="char_anelace">
        Anelace Elfead is a bracer of Bose branch in Liberl. She is the granddaughter of the famous swordsman Yun Ka-fai.
            She is a student of Eight Leaves One Blade school.\n
        In FC, she was a rookie senior bracer. She was one of the bracer who helped Estelle team in many incidents.\n
        After the coup, she became close friend and friendly rival with Estelle during and after their Bracer training at
            Le Locle.\n
        During SC, she was assigned to search for the Society. Anelace, Kurt, Grant, and Karna managed to find a local
            hideout of the Society in Liberl and went to spy on them. However, they were found out and only Kurt managed to
            escape and send the message to Estelle team. Anelace and the rest were later rescued.\n
        In 3rd chapter, it was revealed that she was struggling to understand her path of sword. Cassius Bright and Richard, as
            senior of the school, helped her to choose her own path.
    </string>

    <string name="char_bleublanc">
        Bleublanc, known as the Phantom Thief B, is Enforcer No. X of Ouroboros.\n
        He is a narcissistic and egotistical to a point. He has vain ideas about beauty and attributes it with pride and sees
            Olivier as his rival. He admired Princess Klaudia\'s beauty and admits that he is in love with her.\n
        In FC, he does not appear officially but he has stolen several artworks and tested Estelle team to bring them back by
            solving his puzzle.s\n
        In SC, he is an Ouroboros member who joins the Gospel Plan. He does not share same interest with the mastermind Georg
            Weissmann but he accepts a role in the plan for his own satisfaction.\n
        After the fight at Liber Arc, he warns everything is just the beginning.
    </string>

    <string name="char_campanella">
        Campanella, known as The Fool, is Enforcer No. 0 of Ouroboros.\n
        He is the right hand of Ouroboros\' Grandmaster, to which he reports the progress of the plans/\n
        He declares that he is merely an observer of the Gospel Plan and has no interest in interfering with the plan
            nor Estelle team. However, to make things interesting for him, he often send enemies to cause difficulty for
            Estelle team.\n
        After Weissmann dead, he only interests in retrieve Weissmann\'s weapon and the Aureole.\n
        In the 3rd, he has a meeting with the higher members of Ouroboros and informs everyone, including the Grandmaster,
            about the plan. During the meeting, it is revealed that the Gospel Plan is considered completed, and they are preparing
            for the next step, the Phantasmal Blaze Plan.
    </string>

    <string name="char_cassius">
        Lieutenant General Cassius Bright, also known as the Divine Blade, is the commander of the Royal Army of Liberl
            and the former S-rank bracer.\n
        He is Estelle\'s biological father and foster father of Joshua.\n
        During the Hundred Days War, he was the colonel of the Imperial Army. He succeeded in protecting Liberl but lost his
            wife, Lena, in the war. Because of that, he gave up his sword and position to picked up his staff and became a bracer
            in order to protect his last living treasure, Estelle.\n
        In S.1197, he was a target of extermination by Ouroboros. The Society dispatched Joshua Astray to assassinate him
            but failed. He brought Joshua back home and raised him like his own son.\n
        In SC, bracer guilds in Erebonia were attacked by unknown forces. He was requested to help solve the incident.
            Thanks to him, the jaegar group Jester was eliminated. However, it was revealed that the sabotage of bracer
            branches was what the Erebonia\'s Intelligence Division wished for. They deemed Cassius as the most dangerous
            man for their currently unknown goal.\n
        In FC, after the coup, he returned to work in the army. Thanks to him and Olivier having a secret deal, they managed
            to prevent Erebonia forces from crossing Hanken Gate during the Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon.\n
        When Estelle and Joshua could not escape the collapsing Liber and were falling to their dead, Cassius rode on a dragon
            to save them.
    </string>

    <string name="char_celeste">
        Celeste D. Auslese was the de facto leader of the ancient faction that sealed away the Aureole.\n
        In order to seal Aureole away, Celeste created a copy of her in Phantasma to slow down Aureole\'s ability to
            process inside it.\n
        Her copy, Aureole, and the Liber Arc were sealed away in a different dimension until Georg Weissman unseal the
            barrier.\n
        In the 3rd, Celeste\'s copy lost her power ruling over Phantasm by the Lord of Phantasma. She seeks help from
            Kevin and Ries who hold the Recluse Cube that allow them to come to Phantasma.\n
        After the lord is defeated, she accepts her fate to rest because she has completed her duty.
    </string>

    <string name="char_colins">
        Dean Collins is the current Dean at Jenis Royal Academy in Liberl.
    </string>

    <string name="char_raven_trio">
        The Raven Gang consists many outlaw young men. However, the most standouts are Din, Lace, and Rocco.\n
        They were the head of the Raven gang after Agate left. Their ill-natured remained until the Estelle\'s
        optimistic nature charm them. Thanks to Estelle, the trio and the entire gang slowly change the way they
        should behave.\n
        During the crisis in SC, Raven gang was a large civilian force that maintained peace and support citizens of
        Ruan.\n
        In the 3rd, the trio decided to become Bracer, inspired by Estelle. Agate was their mentor. In the day they
            had a test to decide if they could become junior bracers, Rocco was irritated by their weakness and blamed
            Din and Lace for holding him back. The trio was almost broken down as Din and Lace left Rocco on his own.
            But they decided to come back for Rocco knowing the dangerous of their test location. Thanks to that, the trio
            finally had a conversation to reflect themselves. In the end, Agate determined them were worthy to become
            junior bracers despite their flaw during the test.\n
    </string>

    <string name="char_don">
        Don Capua is a member of the Capua family. He was an Erebonian noble until a corrupted deal that made the Capua
            lost everything. Kyle and Josette are his younger brother and sister.\n
        After the Capua lost everything except their ship, the Bobcat, they became sky pirates with several other people.\n\n
        In FC, Don first appeared as an evil bandit that even Josette and Kyle were confused and questioned his humanity. It
            was turned out that he was brainwashed by George Weissmann to act like how colonel Richard wanted, in order to
            inflate Richard\'s reputation for catching the criminals that he made.\n
        Don was freed from brainwashed after being defeated by Estelle team. He and the rest of sky bandit went to jail. They
            met Estelle team again when they were in prison during Estelle\'s mission to rescue professor Albert. They also met
            again during the Grancel tournament.\n\n
        In SC, Joshua freed Capua sky bandit and stole back the Bobcat. In exchange, the Capua sky bandit helped Joshua
            infiltrated the Glorious of the Society. After their deal was completed, however, the Capua sky bandit decided
            to help Joshua further more and ended up saving him while he and Estelle were gunning down by battle ships.\n
        Right after the Orbal Shutdown Phenomenon, the Bobcat crashed onto the Liber Arc. They faced the Society while fixing
            the Bobcat. In order to protect Josette, Don and the rest were arrested by Josette was hiding. They were rescued after
            Josette requested Estelle team to save them. Don decided to help Liberl as much as they can while they were on Liber Arc.
            Thanks to that, the Capua sky bandit was under the mercy of Queen Alicia. She forgave all of their past crime, bought the
            Bobcat from Erebonia and gifted it to them.\n\n
        In the 3rd, they were grateful by Queen Alicia\'s kindness and turned to work honestly as sky delivery service.
    </string>

    <string name="char_dunan">
        Dunan von Auslese is a member of Liberlian Royal Family. He is the nephew of Queen Alicia and uncle of Princess Klaudia.\n
        In FC, he was an arrogant person who still believed in the power of a noble. He sided with the Intelligence Division
            to get the right of succession to himself. However, he did not know he was the pawn of the Intelligence Division until
            the coup happened. He was scolded harshly by Queen Alicia and decided to isolate himself in the Erbe Royal Villa and
            reflected on her words.\n
        In FC, he had not changed much but he had shown signs of reflecting his past actions. Princess Klaudia agreed of how Dunan
            judged her for not being capable to lead the country.\n
        After the kidnapping of Dunan incident, he finally reflected himself and changed into a decent member of royal. He
            helped people, and especially worked hard to provide support for citizens in need. He also prepared to sacrifice
            himself to protect Queen Alicia and Princess Klaudia during the attack of the Society in Grancel.
    </string>

    <string name="char_elnan">
        Elnan is a guild receptionist of Bracer Guild in Grancel branch.
    </string>

</resources>
